Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
The current Kira is foolish and
his exchange with the Japanese
task force was far too convenient.
Taking that into consideration...
Kira is probably conspiring with
the Japanese task force headquarters.
Conspiring?
If that's the case,
then Kira is...the new L.
Members of the Japanese Task force:
Was there ever a time that you thought
your Second L was Kira?
Near...I've got to kill him-!
Big trouble! Demegawa's on TV and...
I, Demegawa, along with
my comrades have finally pinpointed
the location of and surrounded...
the hideout of the evil organization
that is trying to catch our god, Kira.
Fellow Kira followers!
Do not rush in all at once.
The traitors may hide
among you to escape.
I am Kira's voice.
Follow me and we will corner them...
Place them in front of the cameras...
And offer them to Kira!
I'm not going to miss them!
Near, you have to get out of there.
You have some nerve saying that...
you being Kira.
You're still saying that?
There are other organizations
that are chasing Kira.
We get attacked as soon
as I begin to suspect you.
The timing is too convenient.
Near, you've made some kind of mistake
and are making too many assumptions.
Members of the task force...
Kira is probably among you.
Think carefully.
Light is Kira...
My suspicions are
getting stronger again...
The previous L also
thought that Light was Kira...
The first wave of twenty people will...
Break the door and get inside!
The second wave will stand by!
Idiot, out of the way!
We're the first wave!
What?! We're going first!
Near, we've got to get away immediately.
Really, what stupid people.
I don't think it's strange that
there are people who follow Kira.
They are people who hope that Kira
will bring justice to evildoers.
The people who are barging
in here are different.
They really are stupid people...
Selfish people...
who only want to have some fun.
I know that, but right now...
Let's use L's fortune and
the anti-Kira people we hired.
But if we carry out that plan once...
Let's do it.
We should be all ready prepared.
It should be interesting...
M-M...
It's money--!!
It's money--!
Money?
Wow! So much!
Amazing...
I wish I were there.
Matsuda...
Jeez. Humans are sure interesting.
Well, that can buy apples.
So I kind of understand.
- I grabbed these first!
- Cut it out!
Out of the way.
Damn. Curse you, Near-!
He plans to use this
chaos to escape-!
But then he'll be caught on
Demegawa's cameras...
Pilot! Go to the floor where
the money is coming from-!
Jeez. What is Deme doing-?!
You can't buy love and peace
with money!
A large flurry of money is causing
a panic in Lower Manhattan.
It's the police!
The police?!
As expected when faced with
this chaos the police were called in.
This is bad...at this rate...
Let's go.
Right now, we can just walk out
the entrance.
As expected, the police have to
take action in a riot like this.
Damn... They were prepared
for something like this...
They plan to come out among
the police-!
Telling Aizawa and the others
to watch over the police
is like saying that I'm Kira-!
The police have come out
from the building.
Where is he-?!
He should be among them...
Where-?!
Damn it...
I wonder how much money that was...
Matsuda...
It was probably about 10 million dollars...
How many apples is that?
Near!
Near?!
This is Near.
We've reestablished a connection,
so I decided I should give you a call.
Near, you're safe.
Members of the task force...
I think it's about time that you have
some certainty about who Kira is.
We were attacked at such
a convenient time.
It's like saying that Kira is in
the Japanese Task Force Headquarters.
With this in mind,
you're worse than a preschooler
if you're not suspicious of the Second L.
The number I gave the day
before is working again,
so call any time you like.
Well, then...
I'll be waiting.
He's pretty sure of himself.
Near's pretty bold.
Everyone...
Help Near if you want to.
I'm not satisfied with this situation.
Ideally, we should cooperate
with the SPK.
Near is tripping us up, isn't he?
When I think about...
Deputy Director Yagami,
I don't want to suspect Light.
But...
Dad?
Welcome back.
So you're home today.
Yeah... You're still awake?
I have tests coming up...
I see.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Okay.
You too.
It's not unusual for someone
to want to contact Near.
The problem is after that.
If I'm late to act, something I may
not be able to fix may happen...
I have no choice but to do it-!
It's an emergency order from Light.
Umm... number three...
Huh?
No way...
Yes, this is Near.
This is Aizawa
of the Japanese Task Force.
The time has finally come...
In order to keep me safe and
for me to become a normal wife...
This is what Light wants for me!
He wants me to be happy
just as a woman should be...
Light...Thank you...
I see. How fascinating.
So, that L was detained for more
than 50 days...
and there were two suspects who were
cleared due to the 13-day rule.
Of course, that alone doesn't mean
that they're Kira...
So L just simply released them?
No...L had Deputy Director Yagami,
who was Bureau Chief at the time...
put on an act.
He said that they both had
been found to be Kira and Second Kira...
and were being taken to be executed...
During that, the Deputy Director...
pointed a gun at the suspects and
said that he would kill Kira and kill himself.
We rationalized if they were Kira,
they would kill the Deputy Director
if pressed that far.
Kira is quite impressive...
He used his detainment to
demonstrate his innocence...
Did the suspect volunteer
himself to be detained?
Come to think of it, Light did
volunteer to be detained...
If he did, then it's already decided...
So who is it?
Who were those two suspects?
I can't tell you that much.
I'm still a member of the Japanese
Task Force and am working under L.
I understand.
Thank you very much for
your valuable information.
Especially the part about the
Shinigami eyes
that enable people to see other's names.
It's the first I've heard of it.
It will be helpful. Good bye.
Is it all right? Near, shouldn't you
have pressed a little more-?
I think that his cooperation with us
is fine at this rate. Also...
I discovered something very important...
Deputy Director Yagami and the person
who is suspected of being Kira
are parent and child.
That's the only thing it could be.
It's the only reason he would say
that he would kill Kira and kill himself...
Therefore...
The Second L, and the one
who I think is Kira, is...
Light Yagami.
Light.
Yes.
I'll tell you truthfully.
I contacted Near.
Don't worry about it.
I recommended it...
So what did you say-?
Oh...
No, I won't ask. It was strange of me
to ask about that.
I want to believe that you're not Kira...
Sorry for doing this again,
but I want to observe you until
we catch Kira.
And Misa Amane as well.
I'm going to check your room
right now.
There's a possibility that Amane
has a notebook.
Hold on, Mr. Aizawa!
No, go right ahead.
You can prove to everyone that...
I'm not sneaking around
and contacting Misa.
Mogi...
I also want to make sure.
It would be best if Light isn't Kira, but...
If Amane has any evidence
linking her to Kira...
If that happens...
Oh-! Mochi and Monchichi-!
It's been a while.
Light hasn't come back because
of the Kira investigation
so I've been so bored.
It's impossible for her to have the
notebook on her while dressed like that...
We were just told that there
were explosives planted at L's house.
We think it's a prank,
but we'd still like to check the room...
What?!
Is Light all right? I've got to call him.
You can't.
Why?
Light is all right.
He has something
he has to do right now,
so he handed the investigation to us.
I guess so.
Light loves me very much, so he'd
worry about me if he heard my voice.
Search as much as you like, Aizawa...
You won't find the notebook...
I don't want all this to ruin
the mood we have here.
We're not in a club.
You and Mogi should do as you see fit.
Oh. It's time for Kira's Kingdom.
Kira's Kingdom
Hello, Kira supporters.
I am Demegawa, Kira's voice.
Take a look. Kira's Kingdom shares
its name with this program.
Its construction is going smoothly
Architect's Concept
with your support.
When it is completed...
Let's welcome Kira here!
Boy, that's in such bad taste...
Say, is everything all right?
Yeah, it must have been a prank.
But just in case,
one of us is going to stay back to keep
watch over you for the next few days.
Okay. Thank you.
Mogi, you can go back to headquarters.
I'll stay.
Huh? Why Monchichi instead of Mochi?
Don't you trust me?
That's not it. You're just not Monchichi
since you changed your haircut.
It's not cute.
Mogi!
Yes. Sorry!
You stay here.
We have received over
a million donations...
towards the completion
of Kira's Kingdom!
It looks like a scam...
Yeah. It's no different from
any other suspicious group.
It doesn't seem like Kira...
Demegawa...
he's doing things on his own...
People will begin to drift away
from Kira if he does this.
I no longer need Demegawa...but...
Oh, welcome back...
We didn't find a notebook in
Light and Misa's room.
But...
I understand.
Keep watch over me until
you're satisfied.
Right now...
I shall introduce the Kira's Kingdom
leaders whom I have chosen.
The first one is...
Delete.
We with Kira will...
Delete!
Please save me-!
Delete.
Sakura TV
Please Stand By
What is this-?
Why would Kira kill his supporters-?
Do you suppose that he wanted to
stop them from going overboard?
That might be so.
But, this is horrible.
What's the meaning of this?
There was no chance for Misa Amane
or Light to use the notebook...
Mikami... I can definitely use him!
It seems I chose correctly...
He knows Kira's beliefs, ideals,
and what he does and doesn't want.
He takes action without orders.
I made Misa relinquish ownership
of the Death Note...
Misa has lost all memory of
the Death Note
and I've sent the Death Note
to someone else.
Right now she cannot answer
any questions about it.
She's merely a plain woman.
The question is...
the next owner.
He talked to Kira through the television...
He worships Kira from
the bottom of his heart.
Kira's Kingdom Viewer Survey
Do you want to participate in the next show?
Yes
And understands that
he was chosen...
just by accepting the notebook...
Birthdate June 7, 1982
Age 27
Sex
Male
Female
Occupation
Prosecutor
There was nothing wrong
with my selection...
Name
Teru Mikami
Year of Birth
Residence
Kyoto Prefecture
Teru Mikami...
He's worthy of becoming
Kira's right hand.
Shinigami...thank you for coming...
Now I can punish evildoers with death.
What do you think of Kira?
God
God.
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
You are a woman
the whole world pays attention to.
It must be fate for us to
meet again like this.
I just want you to meet me
and listen to what I have to say.
Somewhere...alone...