Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change the dream into reality
The ending that everybody wants.
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal world.
Members of the ICPO...
I am L.
Regardless of how many suspects
there are,
there's a strong possibility
they're Japanese.
Kira, I have a pretty good idea behind
your motive and why you're doing this.
But what you're doing is...evil!
W-Why that...!
Try and kill me!
- I am justice!
- What's going on?!
- I'm saving the meek that fear evil!
- This is unreal!
I'm the man who will become
the god of the ideal, new world!
L...
Kira...
- I will definitely find you and finish you!
I am...
- justice!
Serial Murder
Special
Investigations
Headquarters
All right then, let's start with
the tip-line reports first.
Yes.
Until now, there have been
3,029 responses
about the murders from
telephone calls, etc.
Most of them are from
curious members of the public...
But there are fourteen people
who say that
they either "know the killer"
or "have seen the killer."
Each account was followed up
and recorded carefully.
But no one had information that
hasn't already been released to the public.
There are also 21 people
who claim they are Kira.
We didn't want to rule out
any possibilities...
So all 21 people
were put on record and filed.
Okay.
Next up: victims.
Sir!
Upon further investigation, we have
confirmed that information
of the heart attack victims was, in fact,
publicly available in Japan
prior to their deaths.
Also...
Concerning L's request that we investigate
the times of death for each victim...
We found they occurred between 4 p.m.
until 2 a.m. on weekdays Japan's time.
68% of them occurred between
8 p.m. and 12 midnight.
Furthermore, we have
a great variation of times
on Saturdays, Sundays, and holidays.
That is extremely interesting.
Judging from those times of death...
the culprit may be a student.
I have other grounds for this belief.
Drawing from the fact that
the perpetrator is only killing criminals,
he's probably driven by
his own idealistic sense of justice.
He may even be trying
to become a god.
You could say that he has
a very childish mentality.
I can't believe that...
This is just a mere possibility.
But please get rid of the stereotype
that the culprit couldn't be a student.
Considering various possibilities
is the shortest route to arresting Kira.
Please continue
your investigative report.
Y-Yes...
Has anyone else noticed anything?
Um, yes...
What is it, Matsuda?
Umm... I'm in no way saying this
to give credit to Kira's actions...
but...for the past few days, worldwide...
and especially in Japan...
the number of violent crimes more serious
than robbery has dropped drastically.
Well...
I suppose that's to be expected...
Anything else?
L, that about sums up
our investigative report for today.
Thank you, everyone.
I feel as if we're closing in on the culprit.
Still, I'd like to make another request.
I want the teams investigating
the victims, news and internet
to examine once more
how the victims' identities
were made public in Japan.
I want to know if pictures of
the victims' faces were shown.
I leave it to you.
Chief...
You seem very tired...
Thanks...
I've been pulling all-nighters lately.
What I said about crimes
dropping drastically...
Now that I think about it,
everyone knows already.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Keep speaking the truth...
Especially when it's about things people
hesitate to bring up.
However, if you had gone
on to say that...
we should commend Kira for admirably
reducing crime rates,
now that might have been a problem.
I-Impossible! Support that killer?
I'm just kidding.
Just as I expected, Light!
Hey! Did you understand any
of that by yourself?
Huh? Yeah, kind of...
Oh, it seems like Dad's home.
Welcome home, Dear.
He's home early!
Hey! At least figure out
the last problem by yourself.
I will after dinner!
Really...
Helping your little sister
do her homework...
you sure have confidence.
Yeah.
There's one thing that gives me
confidence to fight the police
if they move against me.
Welcome home...Dad.
Good to be home.
Light, how are your studies?
Hmm? They're okay.
He's at the top of his grade as usual.
Yes, my wonderful big brother!
Yes, my wonderful son!
Dad, you seem a bit tired.
Yeah...
I can't tell you any details,
but this current case is very difficult.
I see...
Your father is one of the police...
That must be the reason why
you're so confident.
Yeah.
I can hack into my father's computer
from my own without leaving a trace.
I can always keep track of
the investigative situation.
Here it is.
The police are beginning to
suspect that the culprit is a student.
Light, doesn't that mean
you're in trouble?
If the cause of death is written within
40 seconds of writing the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death is not specified,
the person will simply die
of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of death,
details of the death should be written
in the next 6 minutes and 40 seconds.
Is that right, Ryuk?
Yeah, so?
In other words, if I write "heart attack"
as the cause of death,
I can write down the circumstance
and time of death.
Looks like I may be able to provide you
a little bit more entertainment, Ryuk.
Number 148, what's wrong?!
Get ahold of yourself!
Serial Murder
Special
Investigation
Headquarters
What?!
T-There were another
23 heart attack victims yesterday?!
Yes.
The day before, there were
another 23 victims.
One at every hour...
The fact that this has continued for
two weekdays straight...
Means our sketch of the culprit
has become doubtful.
No, anyone could skip
school for two days...
That's not it!
It does appear less likely now
that the culprit's a student...
But that's not the message Kira's trying
to send!
Why one every hour?
And why are all the victims
in prisons,
where they can be easily be found?
Kira is trying to say that...
he can freely control...
the time of death.
But something's not right...
As soon as we began to suspect that
Kira was a student,
the timing of the killings changed as
if to contradict our theory.
Is it a coincidence?
No, the timing is too convenient...
Does that mean that Kira knows
what the police know?
This is obviously
a direct challenge from him!
L is probably panicking by now.
I still have fifty criminals left
especially for times like this.
Oh...
Now, L should be starting to suspect
someone involved with the police.
Kira has found a way to obtain information
from the task force headquarters.
I cannot ignore this fact.
What is Kira's real objective?
What is he trying to do?
But I don't get it.
By getting rid of the student theory,
aren't you at a bigger disadvantage if
L thinks you're connected to the police?
My reason is...
It's in order to find L
and finish him off.
What do you mean?
In human society, there are only
a few people who actually trust each other.
That's true even among police.
In particular, L and the police
don't trust each other at all.
Could you trust someone
whose name and face you don't know?
When L discovers that the findings
from the investigation were leaked...
he's bound to search for leads
on me within the police force.
When he does, it's only a matter of time
before the police get really mad.
On the surface,
L and the police are working
together to try to catch me.
But in reality...
L is investigating the police
and the police will start investigating L.
I'm not the one who's
going to find L.
The police will track him down.
And I will eliminate him!
Serial Murder
Special
Investigations
Headquarters
What is this?!
Letter of
resignation
As you see, these are
our letters of resignation.
Transfer us to a different case.
If you can't, we will
quit the police force.
B-But why?
Why? Because we
value our lives, sir.
By L's deduction,
Kira can kill people indirectly
through supernatural powers, right?
If I were Kira,
I would try to kill anyone
who tried to catch me.
That's because he'll be
executed if he gets caught.
Earlier, in that media stunt,
L challenged Kira.
"Try and kill me," he said.
But L never showed
his face or revealed his name.
Just recently, L ordered us
to find out
if the victims' faces and names
were broadcast in Japan.
That's right!
All the victims were those
whose faces were broadcast
to the Japanese public!
We...
unlike someone we know,
we carry around our personal identification
as well as our photos in our police IDs.
We don't hide our faces,
we're out in the open!
We...
could be killed at any time by Kira...
This is why we wish to be
removed from our post.
Excuse us.
H-Hey!
You!
Wait a second!
Here's the solution to this problem.
Take x squared equals...large x.
You can think of large x's
quadratic equation...
as the multiple of two integers.
We had the FBI come to Japan
four days ago.
They are currently investigating
the police involved.
This is the list, isn't it?
Yes.
There are 141 people within
the police force alone
who have access to classified
information on the Kira investigation.
But one of the 141 people
or someone close to them...
Kira is definitely among them!
Soichiro Yagami (48) DOB 7/12/59
Detective Superintendent,
NPA Head of Special Investigations
Serial Murder Case
Sachiko Yagami (41) DOB 10/10/66
Housewife
Light Yagami (17) DOB 2/28/89
High School Student
Light, you gotta second?
Didn't I tell you not to talk to me
as much as possible when we're outside?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Well then, I'll just talk.
Cover your ears if
you don't want to hear.
I don't have anything
against you, Light.
I think the notebook couldn't
have been picked up
by a better person.
And I have to stick around with you
until the notebook is finished or you are.
But I'm not on your side or L's side.
Ryuk, I knew that much already.
That's why I'll never say
anything about
whether what you're doing is
right or wrong.
But I'm going to say this
as your roommate.
What's wrong, Ryuk?
Why are you telling me
this all of a sudden?
This isn't like you.
I'm going to tell you this,
not because I'm an ally of Kira,
but because it's creeping me out...
Get to the point already...
Someone's been following
you all this time.
He's been getting on my nerves.
He can't see me, but...
because I'm always hovering behind you,
I feel like I'm being watched.
That's a problem.
Ryuk, I'll be sure to finish him off.
Who in the world could he be?
Does that mean that L has
begun to suspect the police?
He must need quite a large number
of people to investigate them.
Even if he had
50 people investigating...
there is no chance that
I'd be suspected of being Kira.
I should only look like
a regular high school student.
But, if I leave it alone for several months,
that possibility won't remain at zero.
I must learn my tracker's name.
When I find that out,
I can get rid of him...
Light...
I'll let you in on something good...
There are two big differences
between...
Shinigami and humans
who have a Death Note.
Do you know why Shinigami have
to write peoples' names in the Death Note?
Why would I know that?
You're really talkative today, Ryuk.
It's because Shinigami receive
the human's remaining life span from them.
You get their remaining life span?
Let's say that there's a person
who will live 'til 60 in the Human World.
You write that he'll die
at forty in the Death Note.
Sixty minus forty equals twenty.
Those twenty years in the Human World
are added on to a Shinigami's life span.
As long as we don't slack off,
even if we're shot in the head
or stabbed in the heart with a knife,
Shinigami will not die.
But, no matter how many names
you write in the Death Note,
your life span will not lengthen.
That's the difference between Shinigami
and humans who have a Death Note.
Hmm...
To humans, that's very kind
of the Shinigami.
That's kinda interesting.
Our second difference is
of probably more interest to you.
Instead of lengthening life,
it's about cutting it short.
Cutting it short?
When a Shinigami sees a person's face,
they know their name.
Do you know why?
In a Shinigami's eyes...
a human's name and life span can
be seen above a person's head.
Name...and life span?
Of course, in my eyes,
I can see your name and
life span right now.
If I convert it to human time,
I'll know how many years it is.
Of course, I wouldn't tell you even if
you stretched my mouth open...
Even if my mouth is
stretched out as it is.
Shinigami never have problems
knowing the names of the people they kill.
They also know how much life
they're going to receive.
Our eyes are different.
That's the crucial difference
between you and me.
Shinigami can also turn the eyes
of whoever picked up their Death Note
into Shinigami eyes.
But only if a deal is made, one that's
been with us since ancient times.
A deal?
The price for a Shinigami's eyes...
is half of that person's remaining life span.
Half of my remaining life span...
Yeah.
In other words,
if you were to live another 50 years,
you'll have 25 years.
If it was one year more,
you'll have half a year.
And since you're neither
Kira's ally nor L's,
you won't tell me the name of someone
I want to kill, even if you see their name.
In other words...
I can't get your help.
Is that what you're trying to say?
Yeah.
It's also part of the Shinigami code.
I'll say this once more.
Give me half your remaining life
and I'll give you the Shinigami eyes.
If I do that...
I'll know everyone's name.
It means that it'll be easier
to use the Death Note.
So...
Light, what'll it be?
I dreamed a dream that no one could see,
I threw away everything that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
that I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
to accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster who doesn't know solitude
Who knew Death Note would carry out
everything written in it so accurately?
L  D O  Y O U  K N O W
Exactly 11:45.
Wanted Criminal
Kiichiro Osoreda
Everything is going according to plan.
The Death Note never fails.