Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change the dream into reality
The ending that everybody wants.
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal world.
Light, another message from the
Second Kira was sent to Sakura TV.
This time it's a video and a diary.
I thought I'd tell you.
A diary? He's moving again.
That idiot.
Can't he just wait?
Did he want the diary to
be shown on TV?
Yeah. This is it.
2006... Last year's diary...
Please take a look at the thirtieth.
30th Confirmed our Shinigami
at the home game at the Tokyo Dome
28th There's going to be something
better coming out than the PZ2, called PZX.
Check for Shinigami at the Tokyo Dome...
I'm pretty sure he's saying he wants
to do that on May 30...
If we air this,
the public will find that
that's what he plans to do.
Furthermore...
he can't see my Shinigami unless
he touches my notebook,
so how does he plan to do that-?
22nd My friend and I showed
off our notebooks in Aoyama
Hey Rem.
Hmm?
Why can't I see my own lifespan
even if I have the Shinigami eyes?
Tell me again.
People who have Death Notes only
need to know
the lifespan of the people they kill.
Just like Shinigami can't see
the lifespan of other Shinigami...
people who hold a Death Note
can't see each other's lifespans.
May 22nd, My friend and I showed off
our notebooks in Aoyama.
If "notebook" means "Death Note,"
then it would only be understood
by me, Kira.
And the police...
will probably pay attention to
the May 30 entry which says,
"We confirmed our Shinigami
at the home game the Tokyo Dome."
I'm pretty certain that the "Aoyama" part of
the message is the real message...
But if that's the case...
Light, what do you think?
I shouldn't say anything carelessly.
I should watch how he approaches this...
Right now...
I can only say that he's an idiot.
He is, isn't he?
It's obvious that he wants to
meet Kira at the home game.
Doesn't he understand that
if we air this there'll be a panic
and the game will be canceled?
To be honest, it's so stupid...
That I'm not sure how to
deal with it...
If the diary is broadcast,
then we'll have to announce that
the game on the 30th is canceled.
But if we don't, the Second Kira
won't make a move.
But if he gets angry that
we canceled the game,
there's no telling what he'll do...
That's all right.
The Second Kira seems to
worship Kira.
He promised the Kira we created
that he'd refrain from killing carelessly.
We can believe that.
Anyway, we'll air the diary and announce
the cancellation of the game...
And also announce that we're going
to close off and inspect all roads
around the Tokyo Dome.
Furthermore, our "own" Kira
will respond with,
"Understood. I'll meet you there."
You don't really think that they would
go there even
if we're inspecting the roads
around the dome, do you?
I don't think that the real Kira will go,
but I'm not sure about the Second Kira.
I can't tell how stupid he is.
Also...
Assuming that he isn't
as stupid as we think he is...
I'll try to see if there might
be another message within this diary.
If there is a code that
only people
who have the so-called Shinigami power
can understand, I can't decode it.
But we should thoroughly check out
the places listed in the diary.
The 22nd, he's meeting
a friend in Aoyama.
The 24th, he's meeting a friend in Shibuya.
We have to prepare for the possibility
that our efforts will be fruitless.
We also have to be wary of
people waiting with notebooks in Aoyama
and people lurking in
clothing stores in Shibuya.
It's as I thought...
If the fake Kira is caught,
I'll have to obtain his notebook....
In the worst case scenario,
I may have to kill everyone there.
All we can do is place more surveillance
cameras in Aoyama and Shibuya
and station undercover officers
on the stated dates.
Then I'll go to Aoyama and
Shibuya since I'd fit right in.
I'll go too.
Light...
It's all right, Dad. I go to
Aoyama and Shibuya occasionally.
And I'd be the one who'd look
most natural hanging out with Mr. Matsui.
And the only person the Second Kira
is interested in is Kira.
So Mr. Matsui, I'll talk to you tomorrow
about going to Aoyama and Shibuya.
All right, Light. Be careful.
This always happens as soon
as I go out and turn on my phone...
Yes?
This is Ryuzaki. Please be sure
to watch Light very carefully.
Please keep this a secret.
Y-Yes... I understand...
As long as there's still
a small percentage of doubt,
we still have
to suspect him, eh?
I'm home.
Light, you're late today.
Yeah...
I'm supposed to keep the fact
that I'm helping with
the investigation a secret...
I have a girlfriend
at the university.
Oh my.
What?!
Light has a girlfriend? Wow!
Hey, hey, I'm an 18-year-old
college student...
Of course, I have one.
You should work on it too, Sayu.
Huh? I-I don't have to go
for something like that.
Light, what about dinner?
The room service took care of that.
What's this about a hotel?!
What was that?! What was that?!
A scandalous statement!
Now then, Ryuk...
I have something to ask you.
Oh... I thought so.
Answer me if you can.
Can Shinigami who come to
the human world talk to each other?
It's hard to say...
If I'm attached to someone,
I think that's against the rules
unless I have the permission
of the person I'm attached to.
We don't have a code
against that, so I guess...
another Shinigami might
start talking to me.
So does that mean if
Fake Kira's Shinigami sees you,
there's a chance that
he'll tell the Fake Kira that I'm Kira?
That's usually not done,
but it depends on his personality.
So I can just assume that
you'll act how you usually do, right?
Yeah. Even if I see someone
with a Shinigami, I won't tell you.
Well, I think what you're doing is right.
Thanks.
Hmm?
So, Fake Kira... Have you thought
this out this far?
What's wrong?
Aoyama is pretty big.
I was searching for ways we
could find each other, but...
On the 22nd, there is an event at
a club called the Note Blue in Aoyama...
Ao means "Blue"...
And "note"...
That's pretty elaborate...
He might be smarter than I thought...
That means I need to be
more careful, but...
right now, this Note Blue
is worth checking out.
But you don't want him to
know that you're Kira, right?
Uh... Light?
What's going on?
These are my friends from school.
P-Pleased to meet you...
This is my cousin Taro.
It's his first time in Tokyo
and he said he wanted to go have
some fun in Aoyama and Roppongi.
I'll be counting on you guys!
He's also looking for a girlfriend.
Does anyone want to volunteer?
Hey, Light...
I'm impressed, Light.
No one would ever suspect
a detective within this group of kids.
Even if Ryuk is spotted,
no one could tell who he's attached to
if I'm with this many people.
It's also defense against
L's surveillance cameras...
And it's not such
a bad way to investigate.
I just have to watch the entrance
of Note Blue when it opens...
Found him!
Is it... Tsuki [Moon]... Yagami?
He's the only one whose
lifespan I can't see.
He's Kira!
I never thought I would
find him so easily.
All right, Rem. Let's go home.
You just found him.
Is that good enough?
I can't just greet him by saying,
"Mr. Kira...I'm pleased to meet you,"
in a place with all these people.
I know his name.
I can easily look him up later.
After all, it's such a unique name.
Born: February 28, 1989
Height: 5 feet 10 ¾ inches
Weight: 119 pounds
Blood Type: A
It's written as "moon,"
but read as "Light."
That's kind of cool.
He sure is amazing,
this Light Yagami.
He won the national tennis competition
when he was in his second and
third year of middle school.
He gave an address as the
freshman representative
at this year's entrance ceremony
at To-oh University...
There's no picture of him,
but there can't be anyone else
with a name like this.
Who would have thought that Kira
would be so young and cool...!
He's better than I ever imagined.
There are so many places that will just go
and sell your personal records.
The world is so twisted, isn't it?
I even know his address now!
So in the end...
There isn't a trace of anything
happening in Aoyama
on the 22nd and Shibuya on the 24th.
The only place left is
the Dome on the 30th...
I didn't see anyone who could
be the Fake Kira at Note Blue.
Could he really be going
to the Dome?
Ryuzaki, Sakura TV just received
another message
from the Second Kira.
It's postmarked... on the 23rd.
I have found Kira.
To all of the people at the television station
and the police, thank you very much.
I-It can't be-!
Where? In Aoyama?
Did his Shinigami find
Ryuk and tell him?
No... There's no way that he could
tell who Ryuk was attached to.
I made sure that no one
was following me...
If this is true, the only thing that
corresponds to this tape
being mailed on the 23rd
is the 22nd in Aoyama
Matsuda and Light Yagami are
the only ones
from this investigation
who went to Aoyama.
Is Light really Kira-?
But we don't have absolute proof
this happened in Aoyama.
He found him?
That's not good.
Yes... It means that the Second Kira
and Kira have teamed up...
We're still not sure
if they've teamed up.
The Second Kira is only saying
that he found him.
He may not have contacted him yet.
Since we've come to this point...
the police will have to send
a message to the Second Kira...
Send a message?
Yes. The police will have to reach out
to the Second Kira
and offer him a deal in
exchange for Kira's name.
Isn't this a really bad turn
of events?
This isn't good...
I don't know how the
Fake Kira would react...
But I have no reason to stop this...
If Kira doesn't know who you are yet,
there is still time.
Don't approach Kira out of curiosity.
Kira will kill you if you contact him.
He'll just use you.
What you can do is reconsider
the value of human life,
and atone for your crimes by
giving us information on Kira,
and save the people of the world
from Kira's reign of terror.
Where are you going?
I'm going to introduce myself.
Oh, this huh...
Oh, I wonder if it's your father.
Coming...
Welcome home...
Huh?
Good evening.
My name is Misa Amane.
I came to give Light an important notebook
he left at the university...
C-Could you wait for a second?
Light-!
Notebook-?! Could it be-?
Pleased to meet you...
My name is Misa Amane.
I thought you might be worried
if you were watching TV...
I just couldn't take it any more...
This notebook...
A Death Note...
A Shinigami-!
She's the Fake Kira...
Come on in.
Huh? Is it all right-?
I'm so happy.
Mom, she came all this way
to return my notebook to me.
Could you make us some tea
or something?
I-I suppose I should.
She's the one
I was telling you about.
Have a seat.
T-Thank you.
How did you find me?
Ah... I thought so.
You didn't do the eye deal, did you?
When you have the Shinigami eyes,
you can see a person's
lifespan and age. But...
you cannot see the lifespan
of someone who has a Death Note.
Well... I didn't know that detail...
Okay, I understand that, but...
What would happen if you were
caught by the police
and Kira's secret was discovered-?
It's all right...
I wasn't caught and if I continue
to do as you say, I won't be. Right?
And I will see L's name...
I will become your eyes...
So..
So-?
Please make me your girlfriend!
Girlfriend-?
Yes...
If I'm not careful with her,
she might kill me...
But...
That's impossible.
There were three times
the usual number of surveillance cameras.
Anyone in Aoyama would have
been caught on camera. Including me.
If we remained together
after that...
Even being together here isn't good.
Try to understand.
This is a picture of me
when I went to Aoyama.
I'm sure no one would
recognize her like this.
So what about your fingerprints-?
The tapes you sent to the television station
all have the same fingerprints.
Those aren't my fingerprints.
I did put some thought
into my actions.
A little while back I lived
in the Kansai region.
I had a friend who was into the occult.
When I told her we should
make fake ghost videos and
send it to several TV shows,
she agreed to help me.
I had her dub ten tapes and
I made sure not to leave
any fingerprints.
I took those video tapes
and put the Kira picture on it
and added sound.
And what is that friend doing now?
If you want me to kill her,
I'll kill her right now!
If you really...
don't believe me...
You can hold on to my Death Note.
You're just holding on to it,
so I'll still have ownership and
I'll still have my eyes.
Isn't that right, Rem?
Indeed.
Now there's no way
I can kill you.
If I'm of no use, you can kill me.
Why would she go this far?
But you might have removed
several pages from the Death Note.
You could be hiding them somewhere.
Why are you so suspicious of me?!
I don't mind if you just use me!
Believe me.
How can you say that?
Exactly one year ago,
my parents were killed by
a robber right before my eyes.
I couldn't forgive him...
the trial was drawn-out and some people
started saying he was falsely accused...
That's when Kira punished him...
Kira...means everything to me.
I just... I just wanted to
meet you so badly!
I wanted to thank you.
All these irrational methods
just to meet Kira...
But at least she can get
around surveillance cameras
and keep her fingerprints
off the evidence.
She's not as stupid as I thought...
She even says that she'll obey me...
I understand...
I can't be your boyfriend,
but I can act like I am...
Those eyes you gave up half of
your life for, to meet me and to help me,
will be a valuable weapon.
Thank you...
I'll try hard to make you love me.
I dreamed a dream that no one could see,
I threw away everything that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
that I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
to accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster who doesn't know solitude
Ryuzaki...
you're a friend I have much
in common with.
I've been lonely since you've been
taking breaks from school.
I'd like to play tennis with you again.