Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
How many seconds has it been since
you wrote the first name?
35...
36...
37...
38!
39!
Near, I win.
40!
We're not dead...
A minute's passed...
We're not dead!
I've been telling you that
nobody would die.
Wh-Why-?
Why won't they die?!
G-God...
I did as you told me-!
Rester, Gevanni, apprehend Mikami.
Gevanni, the notebook.
See for yourselves.
Kanzo Mogi
Touta Matsuda
Hideki Ide Shuichi
The first four names are unmistakably
the real names of the SPK members.
Shuichi Aizawa
And the only name not here is...
Light Yagami.
Mikami called you "God,"
and said that he did
as you told him to...
This proves it.
It's a trap!
This is a trap!
Near set the whole thing up
to frame me!
It's strange that no one's dead
even after their names
were written in the notebook.
That proves that this is a trap!
But I told you that nobody would die
because I tampered
with the notebook.
N-No...
This is impossible!
This is a setup.
I don't know that man.
Light, it's too late.
Near wins.
A second ago you said "l win."
That's as good a confession as any.
Light...
Wh-Why-?
S-Stop...
Light Yagami... L...
Kira...
You lose.
You declared your victory
a moment ago.
Truthfully, you might have won...
I might have lost.
We tampered with the fake notebook
as you expected us to.
But when I said that
I had tampered with it,
I was referring to
the real notebook as well.
We only switched a part
of the fake notebook.
But as for the real one...
We switched the whole thing.
This is the real notebook.
I-Impossible-!
We used the same pen as Mikami,
copied Mikami's handwriting perfectly,
and made the inside and
outside look exactly the same...
Gevanni was able to do it
in a single night.
Since I had already touched
the real notebook...
I could see the Shinigami...
Shinigami, pleased to meet you.
I'm Near.
Pleased to meet you. I'm Ryuk.
He can talk to Ryuk...
He can see him, so it must be real...
The edges of this page of
the notebook are cut.
Would someone die if his name were
written on this clipped portion?
Yeah. That person would die.
I thought so...
You probably found many ways
to use this...
I wonder how many times you've killed
and deceived us with this...
Light Yagami. You are Kira.
Th-This has got to be a trick...
Could it be that Mikami betrayed me-?
You're mistaken.
This is happening thanks to Mello.
I'm sure you'll understand
what I mean by that.
Mello?!
Take a good look at this...
Kiyomi Takada burns self to death
Takada's name is in the notebook-!
A plan to kill Takada...
a minute after I did-!
January 26
2:33 PM
Could it be that Mikami did
the same thing at that time-?!
G-God, I thought that you were being
watched and couldn't take action...
I thought it was my job to take care
of Takada in a situation like that...
Idiot-!
I've been giving you orders to not
make any unnecessary moves until today!
That's right.
On the 26th, right after Takada's
kidnapping was broadcast...
Mikami went to the bank...
According to my findings,
Mikami goes to the bank every month
on the 25th.
It is very odd for someone
as methodical as Mikami
to go there for two days in a row.
I followed Mikami to a safe deposit box.
It was only at this time that...
he became clearly concerned
that someone was following him...
It was easy to open the safe.
Inside it...
The real notebook was there and
Takada's name was written in it...
Light Yagami.
You didn't notice that Mikami
took the liberty and made a move...
because you had just killed her
with a clipping from the notebook...
This is when I noticed the possibility
of a fake notebook...
Thanks to Mello...
Who was the one
who created this situation.
Mello may have known about it...
He said that it's straightforward if
we can get him to write in the notebook?
Yes...
I'm going to have to do it.
Mello knew...
He knew that alone, we aren't able
to attain our goal, to surpass L,...
But together...
Together we can stand with L.
Together we can surpass L!
And right now, we are
confronting Kira who defeated L...
with solid evidence!
Try to talk your way out
of this if you can.
That's right...
I'm Kira.
That's right. I'm Kira.
So what are you going to do?
Are you going to kill me here?
Listen... I'm Kira.
And...
I'm the god of the new world!
Kira is the law of
the world right now.
Kira is maintaining order.
I am already Justice.
The human race and the world's
only hope.
Are you going to kill me?
Is that really the right thing to do?
Since Kira appeared six years ago...
wars have stopped and global crime rates
have decreased by 70 percent.
But the world is still rotten!
There are still too many
rotten people...
Someone's got to do it.
When I got the notebook,
I knew I had to do it!
No, I was the only one
who could do it!
I know that killing people
is a crime...
But this is the only way
to fix the world!
This is a duty given to me!
I'm the only one who can do this!
Could anyone else have done it?!
Could they have done this much?!
Could they have continued on?!
That's right...
The only one who can create
the new world...
is me.
No. You are just a murderer.
And this notebook is
the worst murder weapon in history.
You've yielded to the power
of the Shinigami and the notebook.
You're just a crazy serial killer
who has confused himself with a god.
That's all you are...
Nothing more, nothing less.
They're all fools who don't understand.
Near.
The notebook you have right now,
and the notebook that
Aizawa brought from the
Japanese Investigative Headquarters...
Are they real?
Is he bluffing now?
Only I know where
the real notebook is...
If you're going to defeat Kira...
even if it's just to test
the notebook that Aizawa's carrying...
you should write my name or
Mikami's in it.
To see if the notebook is real...
or fake!
He's hidden a piece of the notebook!
Matsuda-!
You idiot! Matsuda!
Who do you think you're shooting at?!
Stop fooling around-!
What was it all for-?
What in the world did
your Dad die for-?
Dad?!
Oh, you mean Soichiro Yagami?!
That's right, Matsuda!
Overly earnest people with
a strong sense of justice like that
are always going to lose.
Are you okay with
a world like that?!
Kill the others if you understand!
Shoot!
You let your father die...
How can you act as if
it were nothing?!
He's writing with his blood!
I'm going to kill you!
We have to kill him!
Matsuda!
Damn...
What...is this?!
Mikami... What are you doing?!
Write!
Kill...them!
Near, it's finally over, isn't it?
Yes.
What happened to Misa?!
What about Takada?!
S-Someone...
What in the world should l...?
M-Mikami is...
Stop the bleeding!
No, but...
We can't do anything anymore...
Light!
Light! Wait!
Mr. Aizawa!
He probably doesn't have
any more notebooks hidden.
He can't go very far
with those wounds.
He'll stop on his own
if we leave him alone.
Near, I'm not taking your orders.
All right. I'll leave it to you.
You lose, Light.
I told you when we first met,
that I'd be the one writing
your name...
in my notebook when you die.
It's the agreement that's
made between
a Shinigami who brings a notebook
to the Human World...
and the first human
who picks up the notebook.
I don't know when you die
if they'll put you in prison.
And it's too much of
a pain to wait around.
It's all over.
You should die right here.
We've eased each other's boredom
for quite a while.
It's been quite...fun.
Light Yagami