Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change the dream into reality
The ending that everybody wants.
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal world.
The human whose name is written
in this note shall die.
Please...
- Stop!
- Now let's see...
Takuo Shibuimaru
Accidental Death
What'll happen!
The Death Note is real!
Don't think for a moment,
that any human who's used the
Death Note can go to Heaven, or Hell.
I want the world to know...
of my existence!
That there is someone is
passing judgment on them!
And I will become...
the god of this new world!
I had no idea what he was thinking,
so I'm through with him.
Really? Then how was it
with that other old guy?
Mr. Yagami.
Please translate that sentence
into Japanese.
Yes.
"When finally, he fully succeeded
in making his dream a reality,
he was immersed in beatitude."
Very good.
As usual, a perfect answer.
Well then, class is dismissed.
It's finally over.
School sure is boring.
Hey, Light!
Light, are you listening to me?
Don't talk to me.
Others can hear my voice
when I talk unlike yours.
You're so boring.
Hey, Light! We're going to go--
Sorry, I have something to do.
You don't have anything to do.
Aren't you just going home
like you usually do?
What are you talking about?
I have something to do.
Something very important.
Yamada is suspected of stabbing
a fellow employee in the abdomen
at a restaurant in Kabukicho,
Shinjuku, yesterday.
The knife was from the restaurant
and was roughly twelve inches long.
- Hey!
- The suspect said...
- Hey, Light!
- "he was being rude, so I just lost it."
What is it?
You sure are working very hard.
I can't waste any time.
I only have a limited amount of time
to write names in the notebook...
The only time I have is when I get
home from school and until I go to bed.
I also need to maintain my grades.
I can't sleep during class.
I need to do all of my homework
for school and my prep classes.
Lack of sleep is dangerous.
It'll affect my health and concentration.
After all, I'm trying to change
this world into a utopia without evil.
There's never enough time.
Huh? Why did you lock the door, Light?
It's Sayu.
What is it?
Help me with my homework.
Okay, sure.
It's on quadratic equations.
I'm sorry if you were studying.
But...it just doesn't make
any sense.
Please help me.
All right.
Light, be careful.
Any human who touches
the notebook in your drawer...
will be able to see me.
He waits to tell me that
crucial detail now? Damn Shinigami!
What's wrong, Light?
Hm? It's nothing.
Well, what exactly
don't you understand?
Well, umm...
I think everything.
From what we know,
there have been 52 deaths
just this past week.
They all had heart attacks.
They're all criminals who were wanted
or being held in prison.
There are probably other criminals
whose deaths are still unaccounted for.
Does that mean the death toll
could easily be over a hundred?
Chief...we've already started.
I know.
I had a call from headquarters.
At any rate...
they were all criminals who
probably would have been executed.
Perhaps we shouldn't
concern ourselves...
How stupid!
It doesn't matter if
they're criminals or on death row.
Killing them is murder.
We aren't even sure that
they were murdered.
There's no way over 100 people
could have heart attacks at the same time!
It has got to be murder.
Is it even possible to kill
that many people at the same time?
We believe that a large organization
carefully orchestrated these killings.
If you say a large organization is involved,
I can't help but think that
the FBI or CIA is involved.
I dare you to say that again!
Now, now.
Let's stop joking around.
We have to first clarify if these
are murders,
or strange coincidences.
But don't all the autopsy reports
say that
the deaths were caused
by inexplicable heart attacks?
I don't see what else can be learned
from just the way they died.
That's right!
It would be worth looking into
if they were stabbed with knives!
If that's the case,
we'll just have to have L solve this!
Chief, what is L?
This is your first time at
this conference, isn't it?
No one knows L's name, location
or what he looks like.
But he's managed to solve every case
he's taken, no matter how difficult it is.
He's cracked many of
the world's unsolved cases.
He's our trump card,
the ace in the hole.
Our last hope.
Something like that.
But isn't L an arrogant individual who'll
only take on cases he's interested in?
That's right.
We can't even contact him.
L is already involved.
L is already investigating this case.
Huh? Watari?
Watari?
He's the only man who can contact L.
Furthermore, Watari's identity
is also unknown...
Please be silent.
L will now speak.
Members of the ICPO...
I am L.
What are we doing sneaking around
in such a desolate place, Light?
People who touch the Death Note
can see you, can't they?
I can't just walk around with
something this dangerous.
Up until now, I thought that if
my family saw the notebook...
I could pass it off as
a record of cases
which I'm using to study
to become a detective.
But I'm walking a fine line
right now.
If I'm not careful,
I might end up killing...
my own family.
This case is unprecedented
in scope and difficulty because...
it involves more people than
any other case has before.
It is also an unforgivable crime
of serial murder.
In order to solve this case,
I need the ICPO... no, various
worldwide organizations, to cooperate fully.
I want you to decide whether
you'll support me at this conference.
Also...I strongly desire to work
with the Japanese Police.
Huh?
W-Why Japan?
Regardless of how many
suspects there are,
there's a strong possibility
they're Japanese.
Even if they aren't Japanese,
they are hiding in Japan.
What grounds do you
have for your claims?
Why Japan?
I think I can show you very soon
by directly confronting the culprit.
A direct confrontation?
At any rate, I would like set up
headquarters in Japan.
That was pretty easy to make...
Hmm? Does that mean you
were able to hide the notebook?
Yeah, in this drawer.
Does that count as a hiding place?
You left the key in the lock.
That's fine.
It's better that I intentionally
left the key in a noticeable place.
It's just a regular diary...
Most people will probably be satisfied
with the secrets of this drawer...
after reading this diary.
But...
The real key... is this.
There's nothing suspicious
about having one of these on my desk.
It's just a regular ballpoint pen.
I'll use the ink cartridge.
That's the key?
Yeah.
On the back of the drawer...
there's a small hole that's hard to notice
if you don't look closely.
You put this in the hole.
I see.
It's got a false bottom.
Well, you also have the fake diary,
so I doubt anyone will find it.
That's not all.
Even if they discovered
it has a false bottom,
there would be no way that
they could take the notebook.
You see...
This ink cartridge is an insulator
so it doesn't channel electricity,
and stops the flow of electricity
in the circuit.
When the bottom of this drawer is closed,
this piece of rubber also
stops the flow of electricity.
However, if someone were to
force open the bottom,
gasoline in thin plastic bags
will ignite at that moment and...
the notebook will instantly
be set aflame.
All evidence will be
completely destroyed.
That's how it's set up.
I can just say the reason
I burned it was that,
"l didn't want anyone to
see my real diary."
It's a believable excuse.
It is a notebook, after all.
I've heard when a human
gets a Death Note,
the biggest problem they have is
finding a good place to hide it.
But, Light, you're probably
the first to go this far.
But that setup is really dangerous.
If you make even
the slightest mistake,
you could be badly burned.
Dangerous?
You're talking nonsense again, Ryuk.
I've been putting myself
in danger from the very beginning.
Ever since I first got a hold
of the Death Note.
Compared to that,
this is hardly dangerous.
In fact, quite the opposite.
It protects me.
Which is better?
A small fire in the house,
or being executed?
Last night, within
the Tokyo West Penitentiary,
Naoki Kurotsukayama, aged thirty-two,
who was detained for armed robbery...
is reported to have
died of a heart attack.
In response to the endless,
bizarre deaths of prisoners...
That's amazing...
Bad guys just keep dying.
It's a little scary, but it does feel great.
But now, we really can't
do anything bad.
I wonder if the police are behind it.
The police don't have that kind of power.
Don't you know about him?
Huh? About who?
Kira... Kira!
I wonder who's going to be killed next...
Kira, kill everyone.
Do you want to send this message?
Send
Name: Rococo
Kira, kill everyone.
Name: Misery
Ryuk, take a look at this.
Hmm?
Someone's already created a website.
"The legend of Kira the savior."
That's pretty cool.
Is this about you?
Yeah.
"Kira" seems to come from
the English word "killer."
I don't like that, but...
I've become "Kira" to the world.
Just searching the word "Kira," and
countless sites like this one appear.
Reconsidering the
Investigative System
Television and newspapers have
only publicized
"the successive, mysterious deaths
of vicious criminals."
Mysterious Deaths in Prisons Continue
Deepening Mystery Causes Controversy
But the people of the world
can already feel it.
The existence of someone
passing judgment.
Oh?
Ryuk, humans are like that.
For example, there's no way that
anyone would bring up the topic of
killing bad people in homeroom at school.
But if someone were to bring it up,
everyone would act pious.
That's wrong.
That's what they're bound to say.
Of course, it's the right thing to say.
Humans must put up a front
like that in public.
But their true feelings are there.
They may be afraid or not acknowledge
my existence on the surface,
but on the internet,
where one can remain anonymous...
Kira is already thriving.
They don't talk about it,
but they all understand.
Someone is making
the bad guys disappear.
Those who have a clean conscience
are cheering for Kira in their hearts...
And those who have done wrong
fear that heaven's judgment
will strike upon them.
It's perfect.
Everything is going exactly as planned.
Notice
The Scheduled Program will be
interrupted for a Special Broadcast
We interrupt this program to
bring you
a special, worldwide broadcast from
the ICPO, Interpol.
Hmm? What's this?
Interpol?
We'll start now.
I am Lind L. Tailor
the sole person able to
mobilize the world's police.
Also known as L.
W-Who is this?
It's finally started.
He's never shown his face, right?
So why now?
It means that L is serious.
All right, L...
We're doing exactly
what you told us to do.
Now, let's see you prove what
you said at the ICPO conference.
There has been a string of serial killings
targeting criminals.
This is the most atrocious act of murder
in history and it will not go unpunished.
I will definitely catch
the one behind the murders,
commonly known as "Kira."
He said he'll definitely catch you.
The fool.
There's no way he can catch me.
This is the Death Note!
If you don't have this,
there's no evidence.
There's no way you can catch me.
I knew that the police would
start investigating
and that someone like you
would turn up.
Kira, I have a pretty good idea behind
your motive and why you're doing this.
But what you're doing is...
Evil!
I'm evil?
I am justice!
I'm saving the meek, who fear evil.
I'm the man who will become...
the god of the ideal, new world!
All those who oppose that god...
they are evil!
L, you're too stupid.
This could've been more interesting
if you'd been a bit smarter...
The entire world is watching
to see what happens if
anyone defies me...L.
Just five more seconds...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
What's wrong?
Why don't you say something?
U-Unbelievable.
I had to check to be sure.
Who would have thought
you could have done this?
Kira, it seems you can kill people
without direct contact.
I couldn't believe it before
seeing it with my own eyes.
Listen to me, Kira.
If you just killed the man on-screen,
Lind L. Tailor,
you just killed a man who was
scheduled to be executed today.
It wasn't me.
What?!
This criminal is someone who
the police caught secretly.
His capture wasn't broadcast
on television or the internet.
It seems that even you
couldn't get information on him.
He got you.
But I, L... do exist!
So come on!
Try and kill me!
Why that...!
- What's wrong? Do it quickly!
- What's going on?! This is unreal!
- C'mon! Kill me!
- Are you trying to die, L?!
- What's going on?
- It's Kira versus L!
It's a live murder!
- Come on, Kira!
- This is scary!
Try and kill me!
What's the matter? Can't you do it?!
It seems that you can't kill me.
So, there are some people
that you can't kill.
You've given me a good clue.
I'll tell you something good in return.
I told you that this is
a live broadcast worldwide, but...
This is only being broadcast
in the Kanto region of Japan.
I was planning on broadcasting this
in different areas at different times,
but it seems that I no longer need to.
Now I know that you are based
in the Kanto region.
This L guy is pretty good.
The first victim was
the killer in Shinjuku.
The police overlooked this case
because it was so minor.
Of all the criminals who
died of heart attacks,
this one's crime
was the least serious.
Kurou Otoharada (42)
Unemployed
Shinjuku Random Killing Incident
Furthermore, his crime was
only broadcast in Japan.
Kurou Otoharada
I have been able to deduce this much.
You are in Japan and
your first victim was your guinea pig.
You're just lucky that you're in Kanto,
the most heavily populated region
in Japan.
I never thought that things
would go quite so well, but...
Kira, it won't be too long
before I can sentence you to death.
L certainly lives up
to his reputation...
Yes, he's proved that
Kira exists,
that the killings took place,
and that Kira's in Japan.
Kira, I'm interested how
you commit the murders.
But... I'll find that out
when I catch you.
Until we meet again...
Kira...
He's going to...
sentence me to death?
Interesting.
I'll accept your challenge.
They both have to hunt down
each other,
but neither of them know
each other's name or face.
And the first one who gets
found is dead!
Humans sure are interesting!
L...!
Kira...
- I will definitely find and finish you!
I am...
- justice!
I dreamed a dream that no one could see,
I threw away everything that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
that I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
to accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster who doesn't know solitude
I'm not the one who's going to find L.
The police will track him down...
Serial Murder
Special
Investigation
Headquarters
And I will eliminate him.
Looks like I may be able to provide
you a little more entertainment, Ryuk.