Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change the dream into reality
The ending that everybody wants.
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal world.
Shinigami Realm
What?
Two death's heads again?
Hah! I win.
Don't hold it against me.
Hey Ryuk...wanna join us?
Join us for once.
No, I'm okay.
I didn't do a thing,
but he still got upset...
Really? And then?
What's the matter, Yagami?
Please translate the sentence.
Follow the teachings of God.
Then the blessings of the sea
will become bountiful...
And there will be no storms.
Today, at approximately 11 a.m. in
Kanagawa Prefecture in Yokohama,
the body of a man appearing
to be about 30 years old
was found in an apartment,
covered in blood.
Kanagawa Police have opened
a homicide investigation.
In other news...
Today, shortly after noon,
Naoki Kofuji, 35, was arrested
in connection with the murder of
a 25-year-old female
he was living with
in the Shibuya district
of Tokyo.
Day in and day out...
the same thing over and over again.
Jeez... so ridiculous...
This world...
...is rotten.
No way! You went to see that?
It was such a waste of time.
I shoulda asked for a refund!
Well, you did watch it...
Death Note...
directly translated, a notebook of death...
How to use it...
The human whose name is written
in this note...
shall die?
So stupid...
This is so sick.
It's no different than a chain letter.
"The human whose name is written
in this note shall die..."? C'mon.
Seriously...
something's the matter with me.
This note will not take effect unless the
writer has the person's face in their mind
when writing his/her name.
Therefore...
People sharing the same name
will not be affected.
If the cause of death is written
within 40 human seconds
of writing the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death is not specified,
the person will simply die of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of death,
details of the death should be written
in the next 6 minutes and 40 seconds.
Humph... So you can let people die
peacefully or make them suffer.
A prank this intricate
isn't too bad, I guess.
Write in their name and they die, huh...
So stupid!
Wait a minute...
If someone actually dies,
does that make me a murderer?
No way. That's impossible.
The assailant who killed
six people yesterday...
at a busy shopping district
in Shinjuku...
has now taken eight people hostage,
including children and teachers,
in this daycare center.
The police have now identified
the suspect as
Kurou Otoharada (42)
Unemployed
Shinjuku Random Killing Incident
42-year-old Kurou Otoharada,
unemployed.
The police will begin negotiations
with the suspect.
Kurou Otoharada
A heart attack in
forty seconds...right?
Well, that is not clear at the moment.
You can't help but be worried
for the hostages right now.
Absolutely.
This has been a report from the scene.
Thank you very much.
What do you think, Mr. Hashimoto?
Well, I'm hoping for
a quick resolution to this.
Oh well, nothing happened.
What did I expect?
Just a minute...
There seems to be
something happening.
The hostages are coming out!
They all seem to be all right!
And now it looks like
the SWAT team is entering!
Has the suspect been arrested?!
Yes!
We just received word that the suspect
has died inside the daycare center!
The suspect is dead!
Dead?!
Kurou Otoharada
The police are strongly denying
that they shot the suspect!
Then could he have felt cornered...
and committed suicide?
According to one of the hostages,
"the suspect just suddenly collapsed."
A heart attack...
N-No way...
This is a coincidence.
It's gotta be coincidence!
Light!
It's almost 6:30. Don't you have
your prep course tonight?
Yeah, I'm getting ready now.
Death Note...
But if this really works...
It's worth testing it once more.
So I guess it has to be another criminal.
But it can't be someone too famous.
If he dies, it's possible news
of it will be hushed up.
I need an immediate result.
Hey, Ryo baby!
W-What is it, Sudou?
Lend me some money...
2000 yen will do.
W-What? Again?
Sudou...
- Shall I kill him?
- What? You refusing?
No, I'd better avoid people around me.
No... Why should I worry?
No one would care if one or
two people like him died.
Now we can go to
the arcade after school.
Maki, wanna party with
some guys tomorrow?
Absolutely!
Hey, me too!
Damn it, mom!
She's not here to pick me up!
Damn it... It's sickening.
Every single one of them...
I'd do society a favor by killing them.
Hey girl!
Wanna come and play with us?
Hey Taku!
You've got a beauty there!
I'm Takuo Shibuimaru.
Shibutaku, for short.
C'mon and join me...pretty girl.
I don't think so.
She doesn't think so!
She's so cute!
C'mon, grab her...
get those clothes off!
You sure?
S-Stop...!
Please!
Stop!
Takuo Shibuimaru    Accidental Death
Now let's see...
What'll happen!
Hey wait!
Taku! Watch out!
This... This proves it!
The Death Note is real!
Taku!
I-Idiot!
He just jumped out in front of me.
Now then...
I'd better get going.
It's been five days...since...
Now then...
I'd better get going...
Huh? Going out, Ryuk?
This place is barren...
everywhere you go.
I dropped my Death Note.
You really messed up big time!
Hey, weren't you carrying around
a second one behind the old man's back?
You saying you lost both?
And do you know where you dropped it?
The Human World.
What?!
Welcome home.
You're early, Light.
Yeah.
I'm back, Mom.
Huh?
Oh... the results of the national
practice entrance exams?
Hurry!
Here.
Goodness! Number one again!
You really did your best, Light!
Well yeah.
I'll be studying, so don't bother me.
All right.
Oh Light...
Do you want anything?
Anything at all?
Not really, Mom.
I already have what I want...
You seem to like it.
Why so shocked?
I'm Ryuk, the Shinigami,
who dropped that notebook.
From what I just saw...
You're already aware that
that's no ordinary notebook.
A Shinigami...huh.
I'm not shocked, Ryuk.
In fact...I've been waiting for you, Ryuk.
Oh?
I didn't think
the Shinigami's Notebook was real...
but after seeing its results,
I can act with certainty.
I see.
You really surprise me...
I've heard of Death Notes getting down
to the Human World a few times before.
But you're the first one to use it
to this extent in just five days.
Most people would be
too scared to try it out.
I'm prepared, Ryuk.
I used the Death Note knowing
it belonged to a Shinigami.
And now the Shinigami's here.
So what'll happen to me?
Are you going to take my soul?
Huh? What's that about?
Some fantasy you humans
came up with?
I'm not going to do
anything with you.
Once the Death Note lands
in the Human World,
it belongs to the Human World.
In other words, that belongs to you.
It belongs to...me?
If you don't want it,
give it to some other human.
But if you do that,
all memory of the Death Note
will be erased from your mind.
So there isn't a price
...for using the Death Note?
Well, if anything,
there is...
only the fear and pain humans who
have used the Death Note will experience.
And when you die...
I'll be the one to write
your name on my Death Note.
Don't think for a moment,
that any human...
who's used the Death Note
can go to Heaven, or Hell.
That's all.
You'll find out about it after you die.
Light...
Don't worry.
Go and get it.
What?
I brought some apples,
they're from our neighbor.
Why is it so dark in here?
You'll ruin your eyesight!
What's going on?
Mom can't see him?
That notebook...
originally belonged to me.
And since you're the one using it,
you're the only one who can see me...
and of course, my voice...
Only you can hear my voice.
In other words,
the Death Note is a bond
between Light the human
and Ryuk the Shinigami.
Tasty.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Why did you choose me?
Hey, are you listening?
Hmm...apples in the
Human World are awesome.
What would you call them?
Juicy?
Answer my question.
Hah, I didn't choose you.
I just dropped the notebook.
Did you think you were chosen
because you were smart?
Don't flatter yourself.
It just happened to fall around here...
and you just happened to pick it up.
That's all.
That's why I wrote the explanation
in English,
the most popular language
in the Human World.
Then why did you drop it?!
Don't tell me it was by mistake
after you went to the trouble and
wrote all those instructions.
Why'd I drop it?
... because I was bored.
Bored?
In fact, Shinigami these days
have so much time on their hands.
They're either taking a nap or gambling.
If others see you studiously
scribbling names in the Death Note,
they'll say, "what are you working
so hard for?" and laugh at you.
Writing names of other Shinigami
doesn't work.
But since we live
in the Shinigami Realm,
it's no fun at all to kill people
who live in the Human World!
So I figured it'd be more fun
to come down here myself.
But you sure wrote a lotta names.
But why'd you write down
the cause of death
only for that guy who
was hit by the truck?
Without the cause of
death written down,
they all die of heart attacks.
That's the best thing about
the Death Note, Ryuk.
I can write down
the names of the criminals...
and slowly reduce
the number of evil people.
What's the point?
Any fool can figure it out if someone
is just "eliminating the bad guys."
I want the world to know...
of my existence!
That there is someone
passing judgment on them!
But...what's the point
in passing judgment?
Why do it?
I was bored...too.
Naturally, I didn't believe it at first.
But that Death Note has
the supernatural power...
to tempt people to want
to try it at least once.
I-I killed them...
Two men... I killed them!
Human lives...
shouldn't be taken so lightly!
Do I have the right to
judge people like that?
No...
I'm not wrong!
I always thought about this...
The world is rotten!
And that rotten people should die!
Someone...
Someone must do it!
Even if it means sacrificing
one's conscience and life!
Things can't stay...like this!
Even if someone else had
picked up the Death Note...
would they be able to erase
unwanted people from this world?
No way!
But I can... I can do it!
In fact, only I can do it!
And I will!
With the Death Note!
I'll change the world!
At first I kept writing the names
of criminals
like I was cleaning up the world.
So that in time, no one would do evil.
While those guilty ones who truly
deserved to be punished for their crimes,
die of heart attacks...
people who were immoral
or harass others
will slowly be erased through
illness or accidents.
Then the world would truly
move in the right direction.
And I would create a new world of
earnest, kind humans.
Then you'd be the only one left...
with a bad personality.
Huh? What're you saying?
Ryuk...
I'm probably the best,
most diligent honor student in Japan.
And l...
will become the god of this new world!
Humans...
are interesting, after all.
I dreamed a dream that no one could see,
I threw away everything that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
that I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
to accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster who doesn't know solitude
Kira, kill everyone.
Do you want to send this message?
Send
Name: Rococo
Kira, kill everyone.
Name: Misery
The entire world is watching...
to see what happens
if anyone defies me... L.