Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change the dream into reality
The ending that everybody wants.
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal world.
I'm surprised, Ryuga.
I never thought that you'd
suddenly ask me
to play some tennis to get
to know each other.
Is it a problem?
Not at all. But...
Did you say that already knowing
my abilities?
It's all right, Yagami.
I was once the British Junior Champion.
If I ask him if he's British,
would he think that I'm trying to find out
more about him because I'm Kira?
Fine. I'll give it a try.
Ryuga, were you raised in Britain?
I lived in Britain for five years, but...
Don't worry. There's nothing there
that can reveal L's identity.
Oh, is that so...
Then the first to win a set or
six games wins the game, okay?
All right.
This is just a friendly game of tennis.
This isn't a test to determine
if Light is Kira.
But Kira hates to lose.
Fifteen, love.
Hey, hey, Ryuga.
You're serious right from the start!
The person who makes the first move wins.
What do you mean that you can't say?
I'm very sorry.
Under L's orders,
no one outside the task force can know,
even you, Deputy Director General.
Even what you are doing and
where you're doing it, huh?
I'm very sorry.
Yagami...
It's been more than four months since
this case has come to light.
People are saying that
the police and L are incompetent...
With all due respect, Sir, but...
Can you really call the police
competent for
putting their tails between
their legs in fear of Kira?
You should see how many people
are left at task force headquarters.
If you're worried about
what people are saying,
then try not to let them know that
the bulk of the detectives
have run away from Kira!
Excuse me.
Yagami.
What about L?
Can he be trusted?
I think he's much more
capable than we are.
He's putting his life at
stake right now.
Are they really amateurs?
Who are they?
They're Light Yagami and
Hideki Ryuga.
The two who entered
this year with top scores.
Don't worry, Yagami.
Kira hates to lose, but...
Most people don't like to lose.
It's not just Kira.
Is getting worked up and going
for the win something Kira would do?
Even so, if I lose on purpose,
he'll think that getting worked up
and winning is like Kira,
so losing on purpose is
also like Kira... right?
In the end,
it's the same thing.
There's no way that he would
profile me with this tennis game.
He has some other goal in mind.
But even if it is just tennis...
I will win!
See, you came in for the win.
Game count, four games all.
All of a sudden...
there's an umpire and a line judge.
Sir!
I thought I'd heard of Light Yagami
somewhere, so I looked him up.
It seems he was the Junior High Champion
in 2002 and 2003.
During the Junior High third-year
commendation ceremony...
he announced that he'd only
play in junior high.
He hasn't played in
any tournaments since.
Hey, hey!
So what about Ryuga?
He's holding his own with
the junior high champion.
I can read your feelings,
Light Yagami.
There's no way that this kind of tennis
can deepen our friendship.
We're just going through
the motions...
Just so we can say
we're better friends.
By playing tennis with you,
you will think...
that I am preparing to take a step
closer to you.
And then you're gonna try to
get me to say something...
only Kira would know.
But you'll tell me you'll need to know
if you can trust me first.
And try to get me to give you details
on the Kira case...
If I want to talk about
the Kira case...
I'm going to have to ask
him for proof
that he's currently in charge of
the Kira Case.
So the first thing you're going to
want out of me is...
proof that you really are L
from a third party.
In other words,
- we'll go to the task force headquarters!
In life, one cannot win
just by playing defense.
To win...
You need to attack.
Game set. Won by Yagami.
Six games to four!
Wow...!
As I expected of you. I lost.
Ryuga, It's been a while since
I've played seriously.
I'm thirsty.
And I have something I want
to ask you,
so do you want to go
get a drink afterwards?
I've lost the game,
so I'll tell you whatever I can.
But before that,
I have something I must tell you.
What is it?
Yagami, I suspect that you,
are Kira.
If you still want to ask me,
go ahead.
I'm Kira?
Well, even though I say
I suspect you,
it's only a one-percent possibility.
Leaving that aside,
once I'm sure that you aren't Kira and
because you have
sharp reasoning abilities,
I'd like for you to work with me
on this investigation.
One-percent, huh?
That's well-worded.
Even if he suspects me
just a little,
it still means that it won't do
any good
if I ask him to meet
someone from the task force.
Which means he beat me
to the punch.
He beat me.
This coffee shop is
one of my favorites.
If we sit here, there's no chance
of anyone overhearing us.
This is a nice spot you've shown me.
We don't have to worry about
how we sit here either.
I have to sit like this.
If I sit normally, my reasoning skills
drop by forty percent.
So...what did you want to ask me?
Oh yeah.
That can wait until
you're sure that I'm not Kira.
You can talk about whatever
you want to.
Then excuse me but, do you mind
if I test your deductive skills?
Yeah, okay. Sounds like fun.
Then first...please take a look at this.
These three are pictures of notes that
we believe were written
by criminals in prison right before they died,
while under Kira's.
Please tell me what you think.
This is interesting.
Really, what a childish trick...
The print number is written on
the back of these photographs.
If I paid no attention to this...
L DO YOU KNOW
GODS OF DEATH
And correctly unscrambled
the sentence the way Kira wrote it,
"L do you know,
Gods of Death love apples..."
There'd be a strong possibility that
I'd be Kira.
But just because I solve this code
doesn't prove I'm Kira.
It would be amazing if Kira
could not only inflict death on others,
but control his victims actions
as well.
And there's a message encoded here
taunting you.
When we rearrange the messages and
take a look at the top letters of each line,
they form another sentence.
Rearranging it into a message
which makes sense would probably be...
L DO YOU KNOW
GODS OF DEATH
LOVE APPLES
"L, do you know?
Gods of Death love apples."
But there are print numbers in the back...
When we arrange them in that order...
L DO YOU KNOW
LOVE APPLES
GODS OF DEATH
We get, "L, do you know?
Love Apples, Gods of Death"...
It doesn't make sense and
it's hard to think that
Kira would have wanted you
to read it this way.
Incorrect.
There are actually
four photographs.
When we add this one,
this is what it reads...
"L, do you know? Gods of Death who
love apples have red hands."
HAVE RED HANDS
It's a fake. This fourth picture is not
a message I made a criminal write.
Is he stupid?
But even with the three photographs,
my deduction was perfect, wasn't it?
It wasn't perfect.
The truth is that there
are four of them.
It would have been perfect if
you'd figured out there was another.
Yagami, even though you knew
the message wasn't finished,
you decided that there were
only three notes.
You didn't guess that there was a fourth.
This is also true...
Damn him...
I see. He isn't just gauging
my deductive abilities.
He's trying to get me to reveal myself.
If I latch onto this,
I'll play right into his hands.
Hmm... I hadn't thought that far.
Well, whatever the case,
it's not a message that would lead to Kira.
Gods of Death don't exist.
Then if you were me, faced with
someone who might be Kira,
how would you check
if he was Kira?
I would try to have him say
something
that wasn't broadcast to the public,
that only Kira would know.
What you were doing just now.
That's amazing.
I've asked several detectives
that same question,
but most of them needed
a few minutes to answer.
And...
you immediately thought of a scenario
in which Kira is talking to the investigator.
Your deductive abilities are amazing.
The more impressive my answers,
the more of a suspect I become, it seems.
Yes. By about three percent.
But in that respect, it's made me
more determined to work with you.
Even if you are Kira,
I would like for us to work together
on this investigation.
Do you know why?
If I cooperate with you,
the investigation will move forward,
and if I really am Kira,
I might reveal myself.
In other words, conduct the investigation
while investigating me all at once.
I think it's a great idea...
But aren't you getting
the wrong idea, Ryuga?
I'm interested in the Kira case and
conduct detective work as a hobby, but..
I am not Kira,
and I don't want him to kill me.
First of all, I have no proof
that you aren't Kira, either.
It would be strange for just
one of us to be investigated, right?
Neither of us have proof
that we aren't Kira.
But Ryuga, if you are L,
I'm sure you can show me proof of that.
Like having someone in the task force
or my father
tell me that you are really L
in person.
If you can't,
I can't investigate with you.
You talk a lot, don't you,
Light Yagami?
Typical for someone who hates
to lose.
Seven percent... could he really be?
I never said that
I wouldn't let you meet anyone
from the task force headquarters.
I am currently working
with your father.
If I take you to headquarters,
you'll help with the investigation.
Am I right?
What is he thinking?
Excuse me.
Oh, me too.
Yes?
Ryuzaki, something terrible
has happened.
Light, your father has...
Yagami!
My father had...a heart attack!
Well, see you tomorrow.
I'll bring your things that you need.
Light, I leave the rest to you.
Okay.
You're sure it's just fatigue, right?
Yeah. When I collapsed,
I thought it was Kira, but I'm all right.
I've been pushing myself
a bit hard lately.
Especially since your son
has been suspected of being Kira.
You've told that to my father?
Yes.
I've told him everything.
Even the fact that I'm L.
That's right. He's L.
We call him Ryuzaki so others
can't find out,
but there's no mistaking it. He is L.
He's the real L.
My father is telling me so.
Probably the same L who has
been ordering the police until now.
If I get rid of him and
the investigative team...
No, it's probably not
that simple.
There's no need to rush.
I'll have time to spy from here on...
At any rate,
I have to be the Light Yagami
who is worried about his father.
So Ryuzaki, has talking
with my son,
cleared away your suspicions?
I'll say that I suspect him,
but it's only a little.
I'll explain once more.
Kira killed twelve FBI agents
who were in Japan.
They were tracking those who
were connected to the Japanese police.
One of them was Raye Penber...
There were many suspicious things
surrounding his death.
And I was one of the people
he was investigating.
It's no wonder I'm a suspect.
No, it's as Ryuga says...
There is no one else to suspect.
Your deductive ability
is quite impressive.
It's always quick and accurate.
Ryuga, I'll cooperate with you
on this investigation.
My father has vouched that you're L.
Also, I want to catch Kira
and prove that I'm not him.
Light...
Soon, you're going to have to study
to enter the police force.
It won't be too late to
do this afterwards.
Dad, what are you talking about?
I don't know how many years that'll take.
I promised you, didn't l?
If something happened to you...
I'd be the one to
get Kira executed...
There's no way that
my son can be Kira.
It's hard to believe this is all an act.
No, if it is an act, it's too corny.
Light, listen to me...
The fact of the matter is... Kira is evil.
But recently, I've been thinking
about it in this way-
The real evil is the power
to kill people.
People who attain
that kind of power are unlucky...
No matter how you use it,
nothing gained by killing people
can bring true happiness.
It's as he says.
If Kira is an ordinary person
who gained this power,
then he is a very unlucky person.
Ryuzaki, I'm sorry for
causing you trouble.
I'll try to recover quickly.
Excuse me...
Visiting hours are now over.
Ryuga.
Is there any way that I can get
you to believe that I'm not Kira?
If you aren't Kira, there wouldn't
be any need to do that.
Cut that out! Think about how
it feels to be accused of being Kira.
It feels horrible.
How about keeping watch over me
in a place without even TV for a month?
Would someone really go
that far to clear their name?
That would be no good.
I can't do anything which would
deprive you of basic human rights.
And furthermore...
It's nonsense to take suggestions
from the suspect.
I see...
It's all right.
We'll know in time if
you're not Kira.
Also, during that exchange
with your father...
I thought that you might not be Kira.
Well then, take care of your father.
Oh, one more thing.
I said that I would cooperate
with the investigation,
but I don't think I can do anything
until my father is well again.
I understand.
Well then...
Hideki Ryuga...Ryuzaki...
He's the L I've been fighting.
What is his real name?
Light Yagami...are you not Kira?
Ryuk...
Hmm?
I never once felt unlucky since
I picked up this notebook
and gained this power.
I'm wonderfully happy, and...
I'll create a wonderful world...
I couldn't care less if finding
the notebook's made you happy or unlucky.
But...
It seems people who have Shinigami
attached to them
experience nothing but misfortune.
Then I shall show you
an exception to the rule.
I appreciate that.
What is it? Is this the only plan
you can think of?!
You think that we'll get ratings
if we do any special program
on Kira, don't you?
We've been getting ratings
because we cover stories that
other stations don't!
Understand?
The problem is with the story.
Someone bring me a good story!
But the police are keeping
quiet about this. It's hopeless.
Idiot!
If we don't have any stories,
just make something up!
Director Demegawa,
a special delivery.
What is this?
Who is this from?
This is what I'm talking about.
This is what I want you to think of...
Wow...this is just too good.
"A message to the world from Kira."
"lf you don't broadcast this...
"I'll kill you all, starting from
your company's president..."
Who wouldn't air this?
This is amazing,
if it's real.
Hey, I'm so happy,
my heart's racing!
I dreamed a dream that no one could see,
I threw away everything that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
that I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
to accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster who doesn't know solitude
If I leave things the way they are.
L might be finished off
within the next four days.
God is really on my side.
Only this time, it's not really God,
but a Shinigami, a God of Death.