Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
I'm going to announce my engagement
to him at the Pop Music Festival.
I used to like Kira as well,
but Light's going to catch him soon.
You'll probably get executed.
Send me a fan letter that
I can tell is from you.
Place within it
five blank notebook pages.
Continue killing as usual
until I receive them.
What about after you receive them?
Make a notebook that looks
as close to the original as possible...
and act as if you're killing
using the fake.
What's up with that, lady?
You're wearing such a short skirt
even though it's winter...
S-Someone...!
Delete...
Mikami's getting off.
A man who was harassing
a woman collapsed.
He was in the same train car
as Mikami.
It happened a few seconds after
Mikami wrote something in a notebook.
It's probably...
Now we're sure.
Mikami
Yes...
First we've got to get as close
as possible to Mikami.
But there's something
we need to be careful of.
The...Shinigami.
We must assume that if the Shinigami
discovers that we're following him,
he'll alert Mikami.
But the Shinigami can only be seen
by those who have touched the notebook.
Being careful of something
you can't see is difficult.
Even if it's difficult, please do it.
I understand.
Light is going to meet Takada
again in this room today.
As soon as they began
their secret meeting...
Takada received a phone call from Kira and
the surveillance cameras were removed.
The first thought that hit me was that...
They could communicate
by writing messages...
It looks fine.
There's nothing in this room other
than the wiretap on me.
Y-Yeah. All that's left is the bathroom.
Why does Light care so much
about cameras and wiretaps?
No, why is Kira allowing this
secret meeting to go on?
Something doesn't add up...
In the event that
they are writing notes...
The only thing that I can do is...
Light, I talked to Amane yesterday, alone.
About what?
Light's in trouble now!
Matsuda, you seem kind of happy.
Amane said that she was going to
announce her engagement to you at...
the Pop Music Festival.
What was
Misa to you?
Trouble, trouble! Big trouble!
Matsuda, shut up!
Well, I just haven't been able
to break it to her.
She's nothing to me already...
Misa, that moron.
That was unnecessary...
No, Takada as well.
Why are women so...?!
Already? Is that true?
She was in charge of Kira's killing
before T.
She gained Kira's power somehow
and discovered that I was Kira.
It couldn't be helped.
There would be no other reason why
I would choose such an impulsive woman.
Amane was doing Kira's killings,
but right now it's me.
He had no choice with Amane.
But Yagami chose me.
Takada, believe me.
You're the only one for me now.
"You're the only one for me now?"
That's so unlike you,
such a predictable line...
It's definitely unlike Light...
- to give such a brutal excuse.
- Those are my honest feelings.
- So, Amane or Takada. Which one is it?
- I wonder how many women...
you've said that to?
- Well... He might be dating both.
- Takada, do you really think...
- Two-timing?
- I'm that kind of guy?
Do you think that's acceptable?!
- Hey, I'm not the one...!
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
Be quiet!
It depends on you from now on,
but I'll trust you.
But I'll make things hell for you
if you're lying.
I'll tell Kira.
Kira, huh-?
I know that the world needs
Kira right now,
but I've been thinking.
I wonder if I'll ever
be together with you...
In other words, I hate Kira
because he chose you as
his spokesperson...
It's fine if he kills criminals,
but we're not criminals...
We should have the right
to be happy.
"Together, peacefully and happily."
Say the following out loud:
"But that could only happen...
if Kira wasn't around."
Yeah. If only Kira wasn't around.
"Kira...
"Kira should be arrested."
Huh?
You're right.
Kira needs to be arrested.
In order for us to be happy.
T-Takada, are you serious?
Yes.
But I'll need your help for that.
You'll be putting yourself in danger.
I'll be defying the police,
and you'll be going against Kira
and the whole world.
Is that...all right with you-?
Th-That's one long pause...
It's fine.
"I'll help you if it means that
we can be happy together..."
A big turn in our favor!
Just as I expected of Light!
He brought the conversation from
two-timing with Misa-Misa
to getting Takki to help him!
Mikami is talking to himself!
To himself?
Yes. He's too far away for me
to record his voice...
But I've got visuals of his mouth!
This is footage of Mikami
during his break at work...
Right here. He's saying something.
Show it once more to us
in slow motion.
Shi... ni... ga... mi, huh?
But...
He seems to have reacted
to the scrap of paper at his feet.
He just gave a small sigh.
Here he talks a bit more.
I'll zoom in on his mouth.
That...Shi...ni...ga... mi...
Just...gave...me...
the...note...book...
And...hasn't...appeared...since...
"That Shinigami just
gave me the notebook...
...and hasn't appeared since."
Mikami was given the notebook
by a Shinigami.
But the Shinigami hasn't
been following him.
I see...
Then I guess that'll be it for today...
Yeah...
It's finally over.
Today was really quite amazing.
It's tough to do this for several hours.
And yet you're still smiling.
Then I'll go to the hotel and checkout.
Thanks for your help!
Must be tough for Aizawa,
making all the reservations
and checking out of the hotels.
It's gone...
The nail mark I left is gone-!
Two of the four marks
I left are gone...
The room is the way they left it.
The hotel staff hasn't come in yet...
So why is the notepad
switched with a new one?
They're...passing notes!
Yes?
What?
You want to meet and talk
to Near directly?
Mr. Aizawa, it's been a while.
And also... nice to meet you.
There's no point in saying that
if I'm blindfolded.
He doesn't have any weapons
or cameras on him.
Then you can take off the blindfold.
Near, I believe you.
L and Takada are meeting
almost every night.
I know.
Then what about this?
There's no mistake that
they're passing notes!
Mr. Aizawa, please stay out of our way.
Stay out of the way?
Yes. It's no longer a matter
of simply finding
evidence against Kira.
We must hit Kira with complete defeat
in order to stop him.
Mr. Aizawa, I'll say this bluntly.
You and the task force are
no longer a part of this battle.
But if you still want to capture Kira,
just keep an eye on him
as you've been doing.
Just keep an eye on him...?
Yes. But there is a purpose
to watching over L.
And that's part of my plan.
I want you to cooperate that way.
In order to win against Kira...
And watch...
the end of Kira.
There's only a few minutes left of this year,
but it's been one full of
breakthroughs for myself.
The East West Pop Song Festival
will wrap this year up.
East-West Pop Festival
I'm Kiyomi Takada, your host.
Pleased to meet you.
The Pop Song Festival is about to begin!
Matsuda, have you crosschecked
Kira killings and the victims?
After our Misa-Misa's performance!
She's this year's opening act!
Wh-What is it...?
We're the SPK...
We want you to come with us.
I must apologize to everyone.
Unfortunately, this year's opener,
Misa Amane, has not arrived yet.
- Huh?
However...
- What's going on?
- unexpected things can happen...
- Mogi didn't tell me anything about this.
- at the Pop Song Festival.
Go back to NHN immediately!
I'm already known as the queen
of sudden cancellations-!
Misa-Misa, stay calm.
Mochi, why?!
We need to do this to catch Kira.
That doesn't involve me!
If worse came to worst,
I was prepared to pull a gun on you...
But I'm glad that
you didn't resist, Mr. Mogi.
I probably would have resisted if
I hadn't listened to what Aizawa said...
But hearing about the notepad,
there's no doubt that...
What's going on?
Near.
What is it, L?
Mogi and Misa Amane
have gone missing.
Yes. I've taken them
into my custody.
What for?!
Why?
Just in case.
Near...
Kidnapping and confinement
is a crime. Stop immediately.
Well, Mr. Mogi and Amane
agreed to cooperate.
I'll put them on the line.
Here you go.
Mogi, Misa, this is L.
Light!
It seems that Near's detaining you.
Is it true that you agreed to it?
Yes...
Mogi...
I was against it!
But Mochi said it would
be better if I sat still.
He said that we would
be killed if I didn't...
I understand.
I guess it's fine if you both agreed.
For the time being
I'm excluding Amane,
who was suspected of being
the Second Kira.
Light Yagami...
You know what this means...
No way-!
You're planning to end this
without Misa-Misa performing?!
Have Misa-Misa perform-!
Looks like Lidner and
the others succeeded.
It's past nine...
All right, now it's my turn...
The time that Mikami leaves work
differs only slightly.
He leads a completely fixed life.
So he always goes to
that gym every week
on Monday and Thursday until 9:00 PM?
Yes. He's come at that time
for the past four years,
ever since he joined.
He hasn't even skipped
New Year's Day.
I became a member to confirm it.
Then can we assume that
he's going this 31st?
Yes. He's someone who would
go on New Year's Day.
He's sure to go on New Year's Eve, too.
Gevanni.
Is it possible for you to touch
the notebook on the 31st at the gym?
Yes. I've already checked
the hotel's security.
There are no surveillance
cameras in the locker room.
Then I leave it to you.
There's a possibility that I'll die
if there's a Shinigami with him,
isn't there?
Yes.
We need to confirm it.
That is why I'm asking you to do it.
Even if you don't see
a Shinigami after touching it...
I want you to continue to
watch him for a while
to see whether there is one with him.
I'll have Rester do it
if you're too scared.
No, I understand. I'll do it.
If a Shinigami is with him...
No, I'm already at this point...
I have to touch it...
I have successfully touched
the notebook!
I cannot confirm any Shinigami
at this time.
Commander Rester,
connect me to Mr. Mogi.
Mr. Mogi. According to
the notebook's rules,
how long can a person be
controlled before death?
23 days, judging by the data from
Yotsuba's experiments.
Are you sure?
Yes. I think that Yotsuba's killings
have proven that.
Thank you very much.
Then it is possible that Gevanni
is already being controlled...
and is being made to say
that there is no Shinigami...
I'm going to confront L...
if Gevanni is alive 24 days from now.
January 3
Takada, you had quite some trouble
at the Pop Song Festival, didn't you?
Yes. To think that
Amane would go missing...
"Give T the order to tell you...
"once everything has been confirmed.
"Once you get the message,
"send me a text message
or something...
"that says you want
to meet me quickly."
January 6
A photograph?
Yes. I want to see how it's written.
Any patterns as to how it's being written,
if there are any quirks,
and what kind of notebook it is...
I want to see everything in detail with
my own eyes.
What do you think, Near?
Yes, Gevanni has done well.
The handwriting matches that of
Mikami's records he wrote as a prosecutor.
This is definitely Mikami's handwriting.
Yes.
We can do this...
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
The escort team has been attacked?
Takada, are you all right?
Is it Near again?
No, this way of doing things...
It's Mello!