Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
Near, I think it's time you
told us your thoughts about this case?
The current Kira is foolish and
his exchange with the Japanese task force
was far too convenient.
Taking that into consideration... Kira is...
probably conspiring with the
Japanese task force.
Conspiring?
If that's the case, then Kira is...
The new L...
It can't be...!
Are you serious, Near?
Yes. But even though I say
that I'm serious,
I'm only seven percent sure...
Commander Rester, we have to make
assumptions during investigations.
If we're wrong,
we can just say we're sorry.
There have been fewer crimes
in Japan lately.
My dad told me that if
you do something bad,
your name will be posted on the internet
- and Kira will kill you.
- What's your name?
Come on, if you don't tell us your name,
we can't file a report.
Give me a break-!
Anything but my name!
I'm going to post your names
on the internet.
Kira, please kill.
I will declare this right here!
Kira is justice!
Kira's Kingdom
It is absolutely true that I was appointed
by Kira as his spokesperson.
Some people may try to kill me
because of this.
But!
I am prepared to risk my life
New Japanese Task Force Headquarters
Kira's Kingdom, huh? What a horrible title.
to spread Kira's word around the world.
The world's come to an end.
Persecuting Kira is an unforgivable act
and should be considered a crime.
We should really kill this guy.
If you see someone trying to find Kira,
whether that person is a police officer,
Oh, the president's press conference is about to begin.
a regular citizen, or a criminal, bring charges against them!
What could it be about?
They said that it was
an announcement to the world.
You're always watching TV, aren't you?
We, the United States of America...
Could it be-?!
Accept Kira and will do nothing
to stand in his way...
This is insane!
I did it! The United States has
bowed down to Kira...
What is he talking about-?
Is he afraid of Kira?!
- Mr. President, explain this!
- When was this decided?!
- Give us more details!
- Explain yourself!
- Are you saying that Kira is justice?!
- That's right!
Justice-? I didn't say that.
But war no longer exists
because of Kira...
Criminal organizations are in a state of ruin,
not only in the United States,
but around the world...
There is no mistake.
Whoever defies Kira directly will be killed.
We know that Kira does not
stand for justice, but...
As a country, we will not take
any actions to catch Kira.
T-That's the same thing! You idiot!
You just announced that
you accepted Kira!
Please explain!
Are you running away?!
Can you really call yourself
the leader of our country?!
I don't believe it.
This is the U.S. we're talking about...
It's their president's word.
Umm... I'd like to ask
a serious question.
What is it all of a sudden, Matsuda?
So you're saying that you're
not always serious?
In the depths of your heart,
do you think that Kira is evil?
What?!
What do you mean, Matsuda?!
Honestly... I don't think
he's completely evil.
Do you believe that Kira is justice?
I don't know...
But I think that Kira is fighting evil.
The world has definitely become
a good place for people who live honestly.
You're wrong, Matsuda.
They're afraid of the carnage.
It's not true peace...
I know. I know that!
But I understand the feelings
of those who call Kira a savior!
I've always been...
A weak person...
But I'm a detective.
I can't accept Kira...
I understand that and want
to catch him as a part of my job.
My head's probably messed up for not
being able to completely denounce him.
There's nothing wrong
with you, Mr. Matsuda.
Light, you too-?
What are you talking about?
Kira probably knows that
what he's doing is evil...
He'll change the world even
if he becomes a martyr...
That is the form of justice
that Kira has chosen...
That's probably what Kira thinks.
We shouldn't argue over
whether Kira is good or evil.
We just have to catch Kira.
If Kira is caught, he is evil.
If Kira rules the world, he is justice.
But the world is rapidly
coming to Kira's side.
Soon Kira will be justice.
What'll happen to us?
We've been dissolved because
of that chicken of a president...
No, not even a chicken.
He's not even a maggot.
You've got to be kidding.
There's no way that
accepting Kira can be good.
You're alive-?
Near!
What should we do?
Let him in.
Welcome Mello....
Throw down your gun!
Everyone, please put
down your guns.
It is meaningless for
us to shed blood here.
But Mello killed the others.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Our goal is to catch Kira...
Right now, killing Mello
will not benefit us.
All right...
Have things gone as
you planned, Near?
Yes. You've heard from
Lidner, haven't you?
About the Second L...
I've pretty much figured out who
Kira is because of everything you've done.
Near!
I'm not your tool to
solve your puzzles!
Mello, shoot me if you want.
Mello!
If you shoot Near,
we'll have no choice but to shoot you.
What'll happen if you both die?
Only Kira will be happy.
Humph...that's true.
Near, I just came to retrieve
the photograph you have of me.
Yes.
This is the photograph.
There's only one and there are no copies.
I've already dealt with everyone
who knows your face at Wammy's house,
and elsewhere.
I can't say I'm a hundred percent
certain, but...
It's safe to say you won't
be killed by the notebook.
Is that all, Mello?
Near...
I...have no intention of working
with you.
I know.
But it'll upset me if you
just take my picture and leave.
The killer notebook...
It's a Shinigami's notebook.
Whoever touches it,
can see a Shinigami.
That's crazy--!
Who would believe that?!
I believe him.
What good would it be for
Mello to tell a lie like that?
He would, at least tell a better lie,
or something that has some truth to it...
Therefore, Shinigami really exist.
The notebook I had was one that belonged
to someone other than a Shinigami...
Also...there were fake rules within
the rules written in it.
That's all I can tell you.
Near.
Mello...
Which of us is going to get Kira first?
The race is on...
Our destination is one in the same.
I'll be waiting for you...
Yes.
A fake rule...
Judging from previous events,
there's no doubt that...
the notebook can cause heart attacks
and control its victims, to a degree.
As for burning or tearing the notebook...
The book still exists and
there is no way to test it.
In that case...
The fake rule is the rule
that a person will die if he doesn't
write a name within thirteen days...
Gevanni.
Get me L.
Yes.
It's from Near.
Yes?
L, we've caught Mello.
But he escaped.
However, we were able to interrogate
him a little.
He didn't escape.
You let him escape.
Isn't that right?
No, he really did escape.
By the way, Mello said that there
is a Shinigami attached to the notebook.
Have you been able to
confirm any such entity?
Yes. Shinigami do exist.
I kept it a secret because
I didn't think that you'd believe me.
I'd like to talk to the Shinigami
about some things.
I don't want to talk.
The thing that bothers me
the most is the fact that
there is a fake rule among
the rules written within the notebook.
There's a fake?
Yes.
L, Tell me what you think.
Which rule do you think is a fake?
By elimination,
it would have to be the one
that requires the owner of the notebook
to write a name within 13 days, or die.
I thought you'd say that.
I think so too.
Shinigami. Was there a fake rule among
the rules written within the notebook?
No, there aren't any.
So there's a Shinigami there?
Yes.
I see...
I pretty much get the picture.
In other words, Kira is there and
he's making the Shinigami lie.
This guy's amazing.
He got it right...
Even if the Shinigami is lying,
it doesn't mean anything.
No. It would mean that it was
meaningless to detain Light.
If the rule that a person has
to continue to write names is a fake,
it makes it meaningless that
he spent more than 13 days doing nothing.
But that's wrong!
There's no way that Light is Kira.
The Deputy Director confirmed that he didn't
have a notebook and passed away...
Well then, how about testing it
in this way?
I will write Mello's name in the notebook.
When Mello dies, and if
I die 13 days later, Kira wins.
I don't mind.
What's this?
So it's just a matter of
winning or losing?
Even if testing the 13-day rule
benefits the Kira investigation,
there shouldn't be any drawbacks.
I shall put my life on the line.
If I reject this offer on my own,
it'll give a bad impression...
Wait a moment.
We need to think about that suggestion.
Give me your honest opinion.
It's easy to say that
we should honor human life
and we shouldn't do that,
but I was the one who was confined.
It's strange for me to
be saying that.
This is awkward...
I think that Near should do
it if he wants to.
I want to see
the Deputy Director avenged.
I'm against it. I don't believe
that Kira is among us.
We shouldn't kill anyone
with the notebook.
Yes. We should follow
the Deputy Director's will.
I'm also against testing the notebook.
Near, we cannot allow you
to test the notebook.
I thought you would say that...
And lastly, one more thing.
To the members of
the Japanese Task force:
Was there ever a time
that Second L was thought to be Kira?
If you've listened to the conversation
and want to help my investigation...
Call the number
I'm going to give you. I'll answer.
There's no way that Light could be Kira...
No, I just don't want to think that... But...
If the thirteen-day rule is fake...
it's true that we can't say
that he's innocent...
Near... I've got to kill him-!
It's me.
This is Kira.
I-ls this a prank?
I will read you a list of people that
I'm going to punish tomorrow.
Check it and make your decision.
Mr. President, I am very grateful
that you have sympathized with me.
But that isn't enough.
The SPK is trying to catch me.
I want you to stop them immediately,
and disband them.
At the same time, I want you to
use American police, the CIA, the FBI...
And all other intelligence agencies...
To find out where the SPK
members are hiding.
Let me know immediately.
I will tell you how to contact me.
Mr. President...it is your choice whether
or not you live a long life.
Don't forget that.
All right...
Demegawa! Please wait!
Why are you suddenly going to New York?
I'm going to crush an organization
that's defying Kira.
It's going to be live!
This is an order from Kira.
I had a call from the President.
I don't even know
what I'm saying anymore!
I don't care about anything!
I'll get a 100 percent, no,
120 percent viewer ratings--!
Come on, everyone!
The age of Kira has come-!
The last L was suspicious of Light...
But I'll just be killed if he really is Kira and
I say that we should investigate
him again...
The thirteen-day rule...
Aizawa.
I've known you for a long time.
I know what you're thinking...
You should do what you think is right.
I never trusted L to begin with.
I'm doing what I'm doing now because
I want to work with you rather than Light.
Ide...
I'll contact Near without
letting Light know.
All right...
I'll make sure that no one knows
what you're doing...
Light...I want to believe that...
you're not Kira...
Big trouble! Demegawa's on TV and...
I, Demegawa, along with
my comrades have finally...
pinpointed the location of
and surrounded the hideout
of the evil organization that
is trying to catch our god, Kira.
Right now, they appear to be
hiding within this building!
Behold the power of the people!
The power of justice!
When Near escapes,
I'll write his name in the notebook...
Light...I'm going to do my best!
Near, At this rate,
we'll really be dragged out...
L...
What's wrong, Near?
Is this a plan by Mello to
finish off the SPK?
Or is it because the SPK is
so poorly structured
that even the public was
able to discover your location?
You and your lies...
I win, Near...
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
I can definitely use him.
He worships Kira from
the bottom of his heart
and he understands that
by accepting the notebook, he was chosen.
There was nothing wrong
with my choice.