Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
Delete!
The average Japanese adult
would say that Teru Mikami
was a child with
a strong sense of justice.
One who was able to distinguish
right from wrong.
And compared to
the average Japanese...
Teru was also clearly more unfortunate.
He was a person who
continuously witnessed death.
There is only good and evil
in this world.
That is the first truth that I grasped
from watching the world around me
ever since I was young.
All humans are split into two groups,
that of good and evil.
That held true even in a small world
like elementary school.
Class Representative
Third Year Group A
Teru Mikami
As the class president, no matter what
high goals I tried to achieve...
there were always enemies.
Stop. Stop... Please.
Evil has to be confronted.
Get him! Get him!
At times, it seemed as
if justice had lost.
But I felt happy no matter
what happened to me.
Thank you...
Those words from the victims made me
want to save them time
and time again.
I didn't spare any effort for that.
In the end...
I was able to defend
my sense of justice.
Just let 'im have it!
Come on, come on, come on...
But...
That was the case only within
the world of children.
When I moved to middle school...
The more often I faced evil...
the more enemies
I had to face.
Victims became participants...
Even observers...
became influenced by evil
and became enemies.
Justice must be served.
I must delete evil
in order to do that.
The only one who understood me
and was my ally...
was my mother,
who had raised me by herself.
No...it should have been my mother...
Teru... Not everything in the world
works the way you want it to.
Please stop. There's no reason
for you to be bullied.
There's no reason for you
to be hurt like that.
You'll just look foolish.
Nothing will change,
no matter how hard you try...
My mother was wrong...
She wasn't right.
She was a person who
should not exist...
Then a miracle happened.
The four enemies lost control
of their car
while joyriding without a license
and died.
A bystander was killed...
That bystander was my mother.
The people I denied were deleted.
At first, I was scared.
I trembled from my heart.
However...
I was sure there were some people
who were happy due to this elimination.
The victims definitely were...
No, almost everyone in my class must
have been glad somewhere in their hearts.
I wasn't wrong.
There was a peaceful class...
There was definite retribution
for evil deeds.
It is deserved and needed.
Evil must be deleted.
That's all. Is there anything
wrong with this record?!
- My beliefs became stronger...
- No. Thank you very much.
with my growth.
There will always be those
who have no reason to exist...
No, whose very existence is
a threat to others.
And the older they are,
the less hope I have to reform them.
They can only be deleted.
Surprisingly...
Time and time again,
whoever I decided should
be deleted was deleted.
Was this a coincidence?
Was I special-?!
Such questions aren't important.
Evil must be punished
by the heavens...
If it isn't, then someone must bring
punishment to that evil.
Courthouse
Japanese Constitutional
Dictionary
That is why I became a prosecutor.
A prosecutor is the good
that punishes evil.
Guide to Japanese
Sentencing
That's what I thought.
That's when...
Crime Report
"Mass Murder of
Vicious Criminals"
God came before me...
Everything that had been happening
around me until now
was not a coincidence.
Who is
the
criminal
killer,
Kira?!
Murders of Vicious
Criminals Continue
Kira Kills a Corrupted Diet Member
23 People Die of Heart Attacks
It was divine justice.
God was watching me...
How I did not kneel to evil...
And punished them for me.
When I realized that,
I went to the place where I could
grab God's attention the best I could.
And...
God accepted me.
Not only that, but he
shared his power with me.
I must respond to this...
I'll figure out what Kira wants
and do what Kira would do.
Delete.
Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete.
Delete. Delete. Delete. Delete.
Delete.
Mikami killed Demegawa
before I gave the order...
But now there's no one to be
Kira's spokesperson to the world...
I can't do anything in this situation...
What are you going to do, Mikami?
Kira isn't saying anything...
I guess he's in a situation
where he can't move.
But this is an important time...
We need someone to
spread Kira's thoughts...
Then... I will...
Extra, extra! A new development!
Kira has chosen a spokesperson
to take Demegawa's place.
Take a look!
This woman...
Kiyomi Takada!
Good evening.
This is Kiyomi Takada of News 6.
Starting today, it is my duty,
to spread the word of Kira,
accurately and quickly.
NHN's star newscaster, huh?
Kira has good taste, choosing Takki.
Report everyone's opinions to Kira...
There's no mistake.
This girl is...from Light's college days...
You've dealt with it quickly, Mikami...
But the fact that she and l
had a relationship will quickly be...
No. She's not a bad choice.
I wouldn't have thought of her
because I know her.
Things may be getting easier...
Hurricane
Soon to Hit the United States
The police are calling for
civilians to evacuate.
Mikami. I can definitely use him...
I want to contact him
as quickly as possible, but...
Kiyomi Takada...
I spoke to her when we
were on a debate show.
She was a shrewd host, but...
Her attitude changed
when Kira was brought up.
She has a uniquely rigid way of thinking.
She hates crimes and social evils.
I talked to her privately
several times afterwards.
She clearly...
thinks like Kira...
She is the broadcaster who is
most worthy of being Kira's voice...
Kiyomi Takada...
It would be too suspicious to choose
an ex-girlfriend as a spokesperson.
There was no sign of Light
sending any messages.
Am I reading too much into this?
Everyone.
About our investigation...
I think we should incorporate
Kiyomi Takada from now on.
To be honest,
I was quite friendly with
her during my college days.
Oh?!
He said it himself?!
That means he has no intention
of hiding that fact...
If Kira is giving her orders
to read messages...
It might be our best option to
find a way to get Kira through her.
Kiyomi Takada
Chosen as Kira's
Spokesperson
But Takki is probably
being threatened by Kira.
She may be too scared
to help us.
That's true...
That's all right. I know her
cell phone number...
She'll meet me if I ask her to.
That's some confidence.
So typical of you, Light.
But it'll probably be difficult
to get her to help catch Kira.
I talked to her about many things
during college.
She's quite...
the Kira-worshiper.
But we can use that.
Right now, even the police
say that they support Kira.
But actually they're doing nothing.
So I'll reveal that I've joined the police
and ask her what I can do to
give instructions to Kira.
It wouldn't sound like a bad idea
to a Kira-supporter like herself.
Will it go well?!
I don't know. But it's worth trying.
I agree, we shouldn't ignore
a lead that's right before our eyes.
Then let's do this tonight, if possible.
Light!
I want to listen to your conversation
with Takada.
Yes. I don't mind.
I want you to listen.
We don't know when she may
give us a hint about Kira.
Y-Yeah...
Hello?!
Miss Takada, it's Yagami.
Yagami-?!
It's been a while. What is it?!
Miss Takada...
There's something important
I have to tell you.
Could you meet me?!
I want to ask a favor of you...
A favor?!
Yeah... It might be impossible,
since you're the woman
the whole world's watching, but...
I don't think you would have
called if that wasn't the case.
You're right...
Since we left college,
I've wanted to tell you,
but I've never had the chance to tell you...
But since we've had the chance
to connect through our jobs as adults...
I can't help but feel that it's fate.
What's this job?
I'm with the police right now...
There's also something
I really wanted to tell you in person...
Right now, the police won't
do anything to betray Kira...
Fine. I may have to help you,
depending on what you say.
Thank you. I just want you to meet me
and listen to what I have to say.
Somewhere...alone...
Okay...after the tonight's broadcast
is finished...
All right. I'll find a hotel room.
But is that all right?
Yagami, I thought you were living
with Amane.
Are you still happy together?
Well...
The truth is she doesn't have
the brains to be my partner...
Mochi.
Yes?
Your cooking is good,
and I appreciate that
you'd do anything for me,
but it's been five days.
Yes.
Light doesn't know about this,
does he?!
I'm beginning to get
a bad feeling about this.
Yes...
No matter how much Light trusts me...
Don't you think that most people
would think that I might cheat on him?!
He'll definitely be jealous!
Near and the others told me that
this woman is the Second Kira.
But could this stupid woman
really be?
Kira hasn't tried to contact me yet...
If...Kira is in a situation where he
couldn't contact me even if he wanted to...
He'll try to contact Takada first...
Good evening.
This is the nine o'clock news.
Kira's words, which I am to tell you now,
are to become the law of this world.
Kira will not forgive people
whose existence is deemed a threat.
Additionally, he will not tolerate
people who live wastefully...
and do not use their abilities,
for the good of society.
Huh?! Does that mean that
he'll kill lazy people?!
You're kidding, right?!
You're overdoing it, Mikami.
No, it's too early.
I've got to contact Mikami...
Matsuda, how is it?!
Yes, the sound and visuals
are great.
No blind spots!
- The nine o'clock news just ended.
- See you again.
Light, I'll be heading back.
Okay.
I've wanted to see you...
Oh, excuse me. It's just...
Please have a seat.
It doesn't seem like it's been that long
now that you're here...
What's wrong with Light?!
He's silent.
He'll look suspicious if he doesn't
say something quickly.
Ide...Have you ever been in love?!
What?!
How is it?!
The mood's good.
That's not what I meant.
Sorry.
Kira...
Mikami-?!
She said Kira right now!
Is Kira contacting her directly?!
You should answer it.
Y-Yes...
Hello-? No, I'm with a friend...
There's no one else...
If luck is on my side
I'll get on the phone...
Mikami...can you bring me luck?
We decided to meet unexpectedly...
Someone who could privately
call on Kira's spokesperson...
Pass the phone over to your friend.
He wants me to give the phone
to you...
It was right to choose you.
She's passed the phone to Light...
It's dangerous if it's really Kira!
Hello?
Who are you?!
November 26?! Five pages?!
What are you talking about?!
God!
All right... Mikami...
How much have you figured out?
You can't move freely now...
Yes.
You're being watched right now.
Are you really Kira?!
Is he asking me to kill right now?!
Turn to Sakura TV.
Huh?! Sakura TV?!
Sakura TV.
We're going to call back Kira
whatever it takes!
He died!
This is bad! He's the real thing!
- Mikami...you're better than I expected.
- Yes...
Kira wants to have the room
checked for devices.
I'm removing everything
before he sees them.
What? Remove the wiretaps-?!
It can't be helped...
What... is the meaning of this?!
Now I can talk to you
without constraints.
Huh?!
Listen, Kiyomi... I'm Kira.
That's right. I'm Kira.
That's all...
Yagami is...Kira.
Listen. I won't allow you to ask Kiyomi...
who I am.
Yes. I leave the rest to you, God...
Understand?
I am Kira and that man right now is
someone with whom I've shared
Kira's power.
Y-You really are amazing...
You're the only man I've respected
and admired my entire life.
For you to be Kira...
That's too amazing!
With me...you're...
going to become the goddess
of the new world...
Yagami...
Light, are you all right?!
Yes. Things went well with Takada.
From now on, I'll be meeting with her
and trying to find Kira.
Delete... Delete... Delete...
Delete, Delete...
Delete. Delete.
Delete!
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
Come to think of it,
since the beginning,
this has been a one-on-one
battle against L.
Fine, Near. I'll come out
if you're coming out.
I accept your challenge!