Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
You have to go outside and
get some sunlight...
every so often...
What in the world...
should I do now-?
Ryuk.
Sidoh...why are you here-?
Hey, don't follow me!
I want my notebook back.
Yeah...I figured it'd be that...
Well...to be honest,
things have become complicated
and I don't know where it is now...
That's so irresponsible.
You're still following me?
Give me back my notebook!
I don't know where it is...
If you want it back, go look for it...
Wammy's House wasn't
simply an orphanage...
It was an institution for
brilliant children...
to raise them to become the Second L...
L's successor...
L's successors...
The one who ranked at the top
was a boy called Near.
Near... N... Huh-?
And the boy N mentioned, Mello,
was ranked next after Near.
Near is L's successor...
There's no mistake...
N is commanding the SPK...
No... Mello probably wanted to
become L's successor...
If that's the case, Mello would probably
want to use any means necessary
to get the notebook before Near...
Near is convinced
that Mello is involved.
He's certain that he is...
These are sketches
of both of them.
There are no photographs of them.
L's successor...
I'm still...
fighting L...
At any rate,
I have to figure out
where Mello and his Mafia
associates are located...
I've already had Misa check
a list of wanted Mafia members
with her Shinigami eyes...
Oh! There he is! Someone
whose name I can't see!
Number 105-! His name is listed
as Jack Neylon, but...
His real name is Kal Snyder!
With the Death Note,
I made Snyder send a letter to
tell me where his hideout is...
It should be coming soon-!
Light!
You've got a letter...
He's in Los Angeles-!
I did it-! I've completely
surpassed both of them-!
I'm definitely the strongest as long as
I have the notebook and Misa's eyes-!
Light, I've been a big help, haven't l?
Yeah, I love you, Misa.
The only thing I have to do
is see how far I can control people.
I'd like everyone to notice me...
so I can talk to them.
The owner is Snyder...
I guess I have to make him touch
the notebook...
Oh, well...
What's this-?
The notebook moved on its own...
It's a notebook that can kill people.
I wouldn't be surprised if it were alive-!
Woah!
B-Boss-!
The guy with the dirty clothes...
Is he new?
I'm not a new guy,
I'm a Shinigami...
Shinigami-?
If you want others to see me,
you have to make them
touch the notebook.
He says you can see him
if you touch the notebook...
Everyone, touch it!
There's nothing wrong with me!
Fine... Everyone...
Touch the notebook.
- Woah!
- What's this?!
- I couldn't see him before.
- Boss!
Shall I kill him?!
It's no use. Humans cannot kill me.
It seems that this Shinigami's real.
And it looks like he's telling the truth.
Ryuk. Right now I'm going to
relinquish ownership of this notebook.
Follow the person who I give it to.
What's this? You're relinquishing
your ownership?
Won't you lose your memory
if you do that?
Misa, lend me your notebook.
If I do this, I won't lose my memory
even if I relinquish my ownership.
I'll give you as many pages
as you need.
From now on, you shall be Kira.
Can you do that?
That's fine, but...
what are you going to do?
I'll explain that right now...
Mistakes will not be allowed.
Chocolate is...good...
Hey! So is what you just said true?!
"lf the person using the note
fails to consecutively write
names of people to be killed
within 13 days of each other,
then the user will die."
"lf you make this note unusable
by tearing it up or burning it,
all the humans who have touched
the note till then will die."
These two rules were made up?!
Yeah. Those are definitely fake.
A Shinigami probably wrote that
as a joke before giving it to a human.
We can disprove the thirteen-day
rule by using a single person...
The question is whether this notebook
has passed through the hands of Kira...
If it has, we'll know whether
or not it's fake...
If we know, we can use this rule...
The thirteen-day rule can
be proven in thirteen days...
Sidoh, keep guard outside.
Huh?
You can't be seen by humans
so at least you're useful for something...
keep watch outside.
Got it?
What's with this guy-?
He's scary for a human...
This is Yagami.
This is Kira.
What did you say?
Kira?
The notebook that the Japanese
task force had in its possession
was stolen by criminals, wasn't it?
Do you have any proof that
you're Kira?!
Proof? Now that the notebook
has been passed,
there's no way I can prove
that I'm Kira by predicting killings.
But you'll receive proof that
I am Kira soon.
My notebook.
What is the meaning of this?
The notebook I'm giving you allows me
to know a person's name
by seeing their face...
Got that-?
Calm down...
and... listen to... me...
On November 10, at 11:59 PM,
Every mafia member who I have
gathered information on
from the FBI and other organizations
will die.
I've already written it in my notebook,
so it cannot be changed.
I also know their hideout.
I shall send that information
along with the notebook...
In other words...
November 10, 11:59 PM...
This moment...is your best chance...
to get the notebook back.
What should we do?
If the members of the mafia are going to...
die on the day that Kira specified,
there would be a chance...
I resent the idea of following Kira's plan,
but it's a good plan.
That's right.
But it doesn't...
do us any good just by knowing
when the mafia are doing to die.
Mr. Ide, you know the answer.
We have the Shinigami follow us...
W-We do the eye deal and
kill them for sure...
I'll do the deal.
N-No way--! I'll do the bargain...
I handed over the notebook
to begin with.
Because of that,
I even thought of killing myself...
I'll use the notebook to kill the criminals...
And after thirteen days, I'll die too...
If Dad ever writes a name
in the notebook...
When that happens...
November 10, 11:47 PM
Is everyone ready?
We're ready.
Then... Deputy Director Yagami...
It's time to make the eye deal
with the Shinigami...
Ryuk, please.
All right...
Deputy Director Yagami,
take a look at the photographs
of the criminals I gave you.
Can you see their names
and lifespans?
Yeah... I can...
Your signal to go is when
their names disappear.
We're going in!
So Kira was involved...
I never thought he'd go this far...
My perfect plan is still...
Damn-! What is Sidoh doing-?
Just be quiet and watch, Sidoh!
You'll get your notebook
as long as you don't interfere.
Roy! Skyer!
The notebook is under Rod!
Bring it up to the monitor room!
Don't move!
L, we've captured two of them.
We've also safely retrieved
the notebook!
We're going back now!
No...not yet.
We still haven't found anyone
who resembles Mello.
He's hiding somewhere
in the building.
We've come this far. Use caution,
and hunt him down.
Woah!
What's was that?
An explosion?
Don't move.
I've just blown up the two entrances.
But that was only a warning.
Next, I'll blow up the entire building...
Follow my orders...
It's Mello!
Yagami again, huh?
Maybe I should have killed you?
I never thought I would be bargaining
for the notebook with you again.
Mello... M-l-H-A-E-L K-E-E-H-L...
Your real name is...Mihael Keehl.
Damn it! How-?
I did it-!
Give up, Mello.
I won't kill you if you surrender.
What? Why are you being stupid?
Hurry! Write his name in the notebook
and kill him!
You'll die if I write your name
in this notebook.
Throw away that switch
and raise your hands!
Yagami...
Don't move-!
I only have to write your last name!
It won't take a second.
You idiot... Just write it. Write it!
Sorry... I really didn't want to kill you...
Yagami...you've...
never killed anyone before,
have you?
Gun shots?!
Deputy Director!
Jose! Grab the notebook!
Damn... This guy...
He won't let go of the notebook!
Why...you...
Deputy Director!
This is it, Mello!
Hands in the air now!
Matsuda, are you okay?
I don't think so...
He seems okay...
L, I don't see any sign of Mello
Wh-What-?
Damn. He got away-?!
That's why I told my dad
to kill him quickly...
Dad, Dad-! Please, don't die!
Light...
Dad!
I'm so glad...
Yeah, I'm glad too, Dad.
Light...
I still have the Shinigami eyes.
According to that Shinigami, Ryuk,
I can't see the lifespans of those
who own the notebook...
Light...
You're not Kira...
I'm really...glad...
Of course.
You're still worried about that-?
Dad, don't say anything unnecessary.
That's important, but there's something
even more important right now.
He has to write Mello's name
in the notebook...
Sorry...
In the end, l... I couldn't kill him...
It might not be good to say that
"it's not too late, " here...
No, it depends on how I do it...
At a time like this...I can be
distraught to a certain extent...
Dad! Write his name!
Write his name with
the last of your strength!
You can't just let him beat you!
Dad!
Light...
I'm sorry...
Dad!
Don't you die--! You idiot--!
You're the Shinigami who came
to take back this notebook, aren't you?
Yes.
Even if it benefits
the Kira investigation,
we only need one
of these notebooks...
I'll give it back to you.
People who use the notebook
are cursed with misfortune, huh-?
Well, it's not as if Soichiro
actually used the notebook.
He died believing that
his son isn't Kira.
So I guess he was happy...
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
If Kira is caught, he is evil.
If Kira rules the world, he is justice.
From now, the world will gradually
lean in favor of Kira.
Kira will become justice.