Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change the dream into reality
The ending that everybody wants.
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal world.
You there...
Yes?
I'm here in Japan on
a secret investigation.
Keep this a secret
from the police...
I understand.
I won't tell anyone that I met you.
Including my father...
Well, I'll be off now...
It's just as I thought.
I also don't want the police
to know
that I've come into contact
with an FBI agent.
If my father ever found out,
he'd tell L.
Raye doesn't suspect me at all...
The police will deal with
what happened just now
as a regular accident.
Welcome back.
I'm home.
What's the matter?
Why the big sigh?
Raye... What happened?
Oh...
By chance, I was involved in
a bus jacking
A bus jacking?
Yeah...
A man who robbed a bank
two days ago tried to hijack a bus.
Japan has become a scary place.
Does that mean you were
also riding on that bus?
Yeah.
In the end, the suspect jumped
out of the bus and was hit by a car.
Did he die?
Yeah. Probably...
I didn't have any time to
watch what happened.
Raye...
Hmm?
Do you really think
that was an accident?
What do you mean?
Well, you were on that bus
because you were investigating
someone, weren't you?
The criminal probably died...
Doesn't that mean...
Hey...
You were indeed once
an excellent FBI agent.
But now you're just my fiancée.
You're no longer an agent.
Don't say anything about
the Kira case.
Don't get involved or take risks.
That's what we agreed on
when I brought you with me here
so we could meet your parents.
I understand, Raye.
It's just a force of habit.
Sorry.
No...
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Once we have a family,
you'll be so busy that
you'll forget that you were an agent.
You won't have time
for that habit to pop up.
But first, help me think of something
that will make your father like me more.
Oh...
Are you going to write down the
name of the agent now?
No.
I'm going to write his name
a week from today.
If he died soon after I met him,
I might look suspicious.
It would be better to do it
once they've investigated
more people involved with the police.
For now, I'll use some
more prison inmates to play with L.
L.
There is another dying
message left by a victim.
Please send an image to me.
Gods of Death...
"L, do you know? Gods of Death."
Does he want to say
that Gods of Death exist?
Watari.
Tell the police to keep
watch on the prison.
There may be someone else
who will leave a message.
I understand.
There sure are a lot of humans...
Are you going to do it here?
I'll show you what I've learned
from all of the investigations and
experiments I've done these past few days...
Experiments?
Yes.
I've been testing different killing
methods on the criminals in this area...
Accidental Death
December, 26 8:30 p.m.
Dies by being hit by a car.
First, I write the cause of death
and the circumstances in the Death Note...
Sho Hanekuroda
Then when I write a name
in afterwards, it becomes true.
That's something even I didn't know...
He's here...
Right on time...
Mr. Raye Penber.
I'll kill you if you turn around.
I am Kira.
If you turn around or
put your hand in your pocket,
I will kill you.
I-It couldn't be...
But this voice...
I've heard it somewhere...
I shall first prove to
you that I am Kira.
I'll kill the man
with the glasses...
working at the coffee shop
you are looking at.
T-That's impossible.
Don't do it...
I had no choice.
I thought that if I didn't kill
at least one person,
you wouldn't believe me.
That man has been repeatedly
accused of sexual assault,
but the police have never convicted
him because of lack of evidence.
He was a menace and
deserved to be punished.
You may already have
heard from L,
that I cannot kill someone
unless I know his face.
I could kill everyone you see here.
If you have any requests,
I'll do it.
D-Don't do it.
I believe that you're Kira...
Of course, you care more about
your loved ones more
than the people here, don't you?
Consider them hostages.
Y-You know about her?!
That's right.
I've investigated you.
I shall kill everyone,
including your family if
you don't do exactly as I say.
You too, of course.
I-I understand.
What do you want me to do?
You have a computer
with you, don't you?
Is there a file on the agents
who've come to Japan?
My laptop is for work. I always
carry it around with me.
But those files aren't in it.
Then take this envelope.
First, take out the transceiver
and put on the earphone.
A transceiver...
It's almost like a toy...
But this won't leave
a transmission record anywhere
and we can converse at
close distances even underground.
He's thought this out.
Please take the Yamanote Line.
It doesn't matter if you take
the inner circle or outer circle.
Shibuya  Shinagawa
I shall be observing you
from a close distance.
Even when you're on the train,
look forward.
Keep your eyes focused
on one spot.
Don't forget, I can kill at any time.
Once you're on,
sit in the corner closest to the door.
If it's taken, wait until it's free.
First, I must ask you something.
If your answer differs significantly
from what I expect,
I will kill your girlfriend.
Of the FBI agents who have
come to Japan,
how many are there and
how are they organized?
Please answer
into the transceiver.
I've heard it's f-four teams...
a total of twelve people...
Next, take out what's in the envelope.
Hmm?!
What...is this?
Of those investigators...
Write the name of the agent
who is directly in charge of you all...
in the space at the top.
What is the meaning of this?
What is he planning?
But I have to do as he says.
He shouldn't be able to kill
with just names alone...
Next, open your laptop.
You should be receiving
a file from your superior soon.
A file of all the names and faces
of the FBI agents who came to Japan.
T-This is... What's going on?
Now, like you just did,
take a good look at each agent's face
as you write their names on the envelope.
I don't understand it.
What is Kira trying to do?
What is he doing?
Looks like you're finished.
Now put the transceiver and
envelope with the names on it
back into their original envelope
and put them on the rack.
Now put your hands on your lap
and continue riding the train
without making a move for
about thirty minutes.
When you are sure that
nobody has noticed
that you have forgotten the envelope...
get off of the train.
Why? Why can't I remember
that voice?
Kira...
Who are you?
Light... Yagami...
Farewell, Raye Penber.
Raye Penber was writing those names
on pages taken from the Death Note.
He unwittingly killed
all of his coworkers.
Heart attack
After sending the files of
the FBI investigators who came
to Japan to investigate Kira.
The rest of the agents all died of
heart attacks after the file was received...
L.
We have a call
from the FBI Director.
L, it's me.
I've just got word
from Japan that all
of our agents have died.
They all died of heart attacks.
I can only think that
Kira killed them.
L, I'm very sorry, but...
The FBI will call off
our investigation in Japan.
It's from Chief Yagami.
L.
I have just talked with
the FBI Director.
According to him,
you were investigating everyone
here involved with the task force.
Yes.
What is the meaning of this?
Do you mean to say that
you suspect us?
I decided that it was necessary
to learn Kira's identity.
I cannot condone this.
I cannot believe
that you would spy...
on your comrades...
L, how can we trust you?
Besides that, Kira killed
those FBI agents, didn't he?
Even if they're not criminals,
he'll kill anyone who
stands in his way!
Kira is really just a murderer!
L. Another victim has
left a message.
L, do you know? Gods of Death...
L O V E  A P P L E S
love apples...
Damn you, Kira!
Raye... died...
No, he was killed by Kira...
What? A family meeting?
Even if I kept it secret,
you'd find out sooner or later.
I'll tell you now.
I am currently in charge of
conducting the Kira investigation.
Is that so...?
Dad, you sure are amazing.
That isn't what I wanted to say.
Yesterday, twelve FBI agents,
sent to Japan to find Kira, died.
Does that mean that
they were killed by Kira?
What?!
It means that Kira might kill anyone
who tries to catch him...
It's a cold
and ruthless crime
scarier than anything
we've encountered before.
Many of my officers have quit.
Dad, you should quit too!
I don't want you to die!
That's right.
You should place your life
before your job.
No. I will not remove myself
from this case.
I will not yield to evil.
Dad...
Dear...
Dad, that's admirable.
I'm proud of you.
If something ever happens to you,
I'll see that
Kira gets executed.
Kira will probably kill all who
oppose him,
even if they're not criminals.
We may be killed by Kira...
Think of your lives,
your families, and friends.
If anyone wants to be dropped
from this investigation, please resign.
If you resign,
you will not be demoted.
I promise you.
I want those with the confidence
to stay on the case to fight Kira,
even if going after him means
sacrificing everything.
That is all.
Hey...
What are you going to do?
Yeah...
Yeah, right, that's him.
I remember him because
he said, "Get down."
But I don't really remember
the other passengers...
Is that so?
I understand.
Thank you very much.
If what I'm thinking is right,
Kira could have been
among those passengers...
If that's so, I can find Kira
along the path this bus takes.
Serial Murder
Special
Investigations
Headquarters
Only five people, huh?
Six including myself.
No, I should say as many as
five of you are willing to risk your lives.
I trust all of you who have a
strong sense of justice.
W-Wait just a moment.
L says he trusts us, but...
We don't trust L.
L, we have decided to
risk our lives to catch Kira.
You should know what
we mean by that.
But you never show your face
and just order us around...
We cannot work with
someone like that!
L.
If you want to work with us
and want to catch Kira...
Would it be possible for
you to come here?
Earlier, I said that I trust you all.
Please keep what is about to happen
a secret between the eight of us.
I would like to meet the six of you
whom I trust as soon as possible.
Before that, I want you all to go
outside of the police building
and decide once more
if you trust me or not.
National Police
Agency and
National Public
Safety Commission
Why does he suddenly
want to work with us?
If he's solved numerous difficult
cases by himself,
he should do the same
this time, too.
And judging by the way that L
has been conducting the investigation,
he'll probably send a double
to meet us.
A double, huh? It's possible...
I-I trust L.
I also think we need L's help
in this case.
Me too...
L said from the beginning that...
he needed the police's help
in this case.
Perhaps you could
think of it like this.
L was waiting
for this to happen.
For what to happen?
There were people
in the investigation
who distrusted L
from the beginning.
Then we had detectives
continue to resign
and our confidential information
was leaked...
You can't run an investigation
unless you trust your partners.
In other words,
L was waiting for the task force
to get down to people he can trust
and who will face evil
without fear.
Yes.
I'll resign rather than
join up with L.
Don't worry.
I won't trail you and
try to find L.
I trust L and will try
to cooperate with him.
Me too...
I am currently in a room
at the Teito Hotel.
I shall be switching hotels from
now on every few days.
From now on, I want you to
think of these rooms as...
the de facto center of
the investigation.
If you can agree to these terms...
I want you to split into two groups,
with a 30-minute interval between you,
and come here by...
twelve o'clock midnight.
Kira, we're finally at an
even distance from finding each other.
I'll do this.
I'll make my first appearance
in front of people as L.
If you manage to find this out,
you'll definitely move in.
Bring it on.
I've worked a lot during
these past few days...
Think.
Was there something that I missed?
And what should I do from here?
L, the real battle starts now.
Please come in.
I dreamed a dream that no one could see,
I threw away everything that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
that I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
to accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster who doesn't know solitude
If this woman had spoken
to the police before she met me...
It seems that a god other than
a Shinigami is on my side.