Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
Near, it went well.
I did everything that you told me to do.
Okay.
Matsumoto
"T"...
That is all I have to tell you today.
Very well.
I also have something
I want to tell you.
Yes.
I've confirmed it.
Hm? A text message?
Ooh... It says,
"l want to see you."
I'm so jealous!
I did it! That's the confirmation sign
from Mikami.
I just have to wait for Near
to ask to meet me.
Near... I win!
I predicted from the very beginning
how you would move!
This is Gevanni.
Near, I've checked the notebook.
For the past three days,
he's filled out one page a day every night
past midnight as he usually does.
The victims match up.
There's no change in
Mikami's behavior.
I understand.
Then let's begin.
It's Near!
He called!
L.
What is it, Near?
I want to meet you.
What?
I must meet you to discuss
the Kira case.
But don't you suspect me of being Kira?
You shouldn't want to meet me.
Well...
There is something that I cannot
show you unless I show my face.
Everything will be resolved
once I do that.
Fine. I want you to realize that you
are wrong about me as soon as possible.
The time has finally come
for Near to prove that Light is Kira...
For Light to kill Near if he is Kira...
Let's agree on some rules
regarding our meeting...
Yes. Anything.
First...
All of our investigators must be there...
In other words, everyone who
is pursuing Kira will gather.
I understand. That's fine.
As I said before,
there are a total of four SPK members,
including myself.
Mr. Mogi, who is here,
will accompany us.
Amane will be released
right before we meet.
She will not be told where
we'll be heading.
We shall meet you once you confirm
that Amane has been released.
How about it?
What should we do?
Near, I understand.
We have five investigators,
including myself...
No, Mogi is with you,
so aside from me, there are three.
Very well...
Now about our meeting place...
Daikoku Wharf.
An abandoned warehouse...
on the outskirts of
the South East side...
Nicknamed the Yellow Box.
I've already bought it if this place
is all right with you.
How about it, Light Yagami?
You should be able to
put your plan into action here.
One more thing.
I want you to bring
the notebook you have at
your headquarters, with you.
Why the notebook?
A simple reason.
There's no one to guard the notebook
if everyone leaves.
I promise you.
I will not try to steal it.
I won't even touch it.
I'll place my faith in you
if Mr. Aizawa can confirm that
it's the notebook from your headquarters.
All right.
But someone other than L
will hold onto it.
Because I believe that L is Kira.
I understand. But I will decide
who holds onto it. Is that all right?
Yes. Then all that's left
is the time and date.
The time and date...
the question is what time.
Mikami kills right after midnight.
In the morning he'll probably be receiving
a notice of the people to kill.
Taking his movements
into consideration...
In three days...
On the 28th. How about 1 PM?
One o'clock, huh?
Just as I expected...
Near is calculating
Mikami's movements...
That's fine.
It doesn't matter what time it is.
Then three days from now
at one o'clock.
Yes.
Near.
Light Yagami.
- I know what your plan is!
- I'm going to win!
Sorry, Miss Takada.
I'm a little busy today...
Busy? Does that mean that
you can't stay until morning?
Yeah.
Sorry. The police are going to have
their hands full for two to three days.
How unfortunate...
I've already given orders
to Mikami and Takada...
This is the final order...
January 28 1:00 PM
Daikoku Wharf
YB warehouse
to kill Near.
It's a rebel!
Protect Miss Takada!
Miss Takada, are you all right?
Yes.
He's getting away! Follow him!
Miss Takada, please
get inside NHN quickly!
Don't!
If someone like that was just here...
It's too dangerous
in or around NHN!
Mello!
At any rate, you should
get away from here!
Miss Takada, please get on!
Quickly!
Miss Takada, it's all right.
Get on quickly and
get out of here.
Yes...
Team A, Team B,
follow Miss Takada by car.
The other teams go after
the car that just sped off!
All right! We've confirmed her safety.
Get Miss Takada to car number seven.
It can't be!
He's taking Miss Takada?!
Damn!
You idiot! Stop!
What if it hits Miss Takada?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
One of them is heavily armed...
News
Takada Kidnapped
in Front of NHN?
Miss Takada's escort team and
the police are hot on the trail.
Th-This is really bad...
Is it Near again?
Near, you promised that
we'd meet three days from now.
What's the meaning of this?
No, this isn't his style.
It's more like...
It's Near!
So, it's the cars that
got ahead of me, huh...
How many escorts
does that Takada have?
Come on!
Since when were the Japanese
allowed to carry such big guns?
I'm an accomplice in
the kidnapping of Miss Takada.
Don't you want to question me?
You wouldn't shoot...
Idiot. He probably wouldn't
have told us anything.
Death is the only way to
pay for defying Kira.
This guy is...
The person that Yagami warned me
to be most careful of. Mello...
Mihael Keehl...
Take off everything you're wearing
and put it in there.
Quickly.
I'll give you a blanket.
L, the one who kidnapped Takada...
was not me.
I see... If that's the case, then...
It's Mello.
Yes...
I'll tell you honestly.
The individual I had guard Takada...
has confirmed that Mello was
the one who abducted her.
I'm sorry this happened while
we had an escort with her.
Near... Can't you contact Mello?
No, it's impossible.
I have a method, but...
There is no way that Mello would
respond in this situation.
Let me take off my underwear...
after I wrap the blanket around me.
Fine.
The escort team was forced to
shoot one of the perpetrators.
They are still tracking
Miss Takada's whereabouts.
It's definitely no good, is it, Light?
Yes. Takada's cell phone is turned off.
I want to get in contact with
Takada if at all possible,
but right now, all I can do is wait.
This is the only thing that can be done...
If I don't do it...
We are still unable to identify
the man who was shot.
Matt... I never thought
you would be killed...
I'm sorry...
Light!
Impossible!
Everyone, be quiet.
Yes?
Light... I...
Miss Takada?!
Miss Takada, are you all right?!
The only reason that she'd call me
without notice in this situation...
is because she escaped
from Mello...or...
Light, save me...!
It's all right. Calm down and
answer my questions.
A-All right.
First, location.
Do you know where you are?
I don't know where I am...
I was put into a truck.
It was locked from the outside...
Oh... We went on the freeway and
I once saw a sign that said
we were heading to Nagano.
Right now, I'm inside a building...
Miss Takada...
you are Kira's spokesperson.
Do you remember telling me
that there might be people
who're after your life?
Yes, I remember.
We talked about what
you would do in that situation.
Do you remember?
I remember...
I did as you said...
I did it...
She did it-!
I didn't struggle even when
I was stripped naked...
I did exactly as you said.
I made survival my first priority...
and did it.
Light, I did everything
you told me to do...
Come quickly... Save me...!
Miss Takada...
You know what to do afterwards,
don't you?
Do as many killings as
I can do while I can...
I-I know... But Light...
You can do it, can't you?
I can...
Aizawa, Ide, let's go.
Okay.
Matsuda, take care of headquarters.
All right.
It's me...
Send me as many names as
you can of those to be punished...
My email is...
Yes, yes, I understand.
The fact that she's called me like this,
means that...
she's killed her kidnappers...
Then the only thing
that's certain is that
she's in a situation where
she can't make any moves...
Nakajima, I'm going to go to
the scene of the crime for the case.
Okay.
We've discovered the location
by tracing the call.
Head to Karuizawa by freeway.
Karuizawa, huh?
Damn. It'll take at least thirty minutes.
Hurry. It's Mello.
We don't know what he'll do.
Yeah...
For God's sake...
Aizawa and Ide are so stupid!
They both got into
the front seat without a thought.
This is just too easy.
This... Mello-!
What's going on?!
Kiyomi Takada, Suicide.
January 26, 2013, 2:32 PM.
Burns to death by setting fire
to everything around her...
including the things she wrote on.
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
It'll end now...
No, today is just the beginning.
Kira's perfect world.
Everyone who knows about
the notebook...
will die!