Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
Hey, why are we having more meetings?
I thought we're supposed to meet
every other week?
It can't be helped.
Coil reported that Misa Amane
might know L.
According to this,
it means L questioned Amane...
This is the problem.
He says he's "deduced that
Amane worships Kira."
"Furthermore, Yoshida Productions is trying
to promote Amane as the face of Yotsuba."
"l suggest that Yotsuba use Amane
for its commercials..."
"to extract information about L."
I can't...accept this idea...
Why not? I think it's a great plan.
No, what Ooi is trying to say is...
It's ultimately Coil's job
to reveal L's identity.
So it's illogical for him leave
this to us, isn't it?
Yeah. We contracted him
to reveal L's identity.
Shouldn't we ask Coil
about his stance?
That's right...
Mr. Kida. I thought we'd agreed
you wouldn't contact me directly.
Is it an emergency?
I understand.
If that's the case,
I have a good idea.
Even though the meeting's over,
I still have to punish criminals
when I get home.
It sure is tough being Kira...
But it's become interesting...
There's no doubt that Misa Amane
is the Second Kira.
And L caught her at some point.
If he's letting her move about freely...
It means that she's forfeited ownership
and lost all her memories.
I can't leave her alone.
I'm going to make
Misa Amane my wife.
Money, power, and a beautiful wife...
That's enough to make anyone jealous!
Once we're married...
I'll take out a lot of
life insurance on her...
Would she marry
such a disgusting guy?
Rem, hide the notebook
in the usual place.
Right now, this is the only thing I can do...
for Misa's sake...
All right! Let's take it from there.
Misa, you said that you came to Tokyo
to meet Kira.
- What?!
- Hey!
Misa, please stop overacting.
It looks cheesy.
What-? But that's what's called
a realistic performance...
Just do it over...
Yes, yes, Great Director Ryuzaki...
If you don't do this seriously,
I'll kick you.
M-Misa-Misa...
You're so tense.
You can just call me "Misa," Mochi.
I'm not suited for this.
But it's still part of the mission
to catch Kira...
Misa-Misa!
What is it, Mochi?!
We have an interview with Yotsuba
to see if they'll use you in their ads.
But it's also an infiltration.
I already know.
Of course, don't let your cover fail either.
You're supposed to be a cheerful,
energetic manager!
Yes, I'll give it my best! All right!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Good morning!
I'm Misa-Misa's manager, Mochi,
also known as Kanichi Moji.
Mr. Ooi,
Mr. Shimura...
- nice to see you again.
- I'm very pleased to meet you.
Good luck, Misa-Misa!
- You're really nailing it, Mochi.
- I'll be waiting to celebrate
when they decide to put you
in their commercials!
I'm not cut out for this...am l?
Well... This is our first time meeting,
isn't it, Misa?
I'm John Wallace, the executive advisor
for the marketing department.
Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you, too.
This is a bit sudden,
but I'll tell you honestly.
We're pretty much certain
we're going to hire you.
But before we do, there's just one thing
we have to clarify.
Yes?
We did a little background
check on you...
A burglar killed your parents.
You worship Kira because he killed
the man who murdered your family.
You said that you came to Tokyo
to meet Kira.
W-Who did you hear that from-?
We can't tell you our source.
But this is reliable information.
We can see it written all over your face.
Coil, I never thought
you investigated that far...
Also...
You're still hiding something,
aren't you?
Something that you don't want
the world to know...
I've got to sweat a lot
and pause here...
L detained you.
Please tell us about
what really happened.
It would be a problem
if the face of Yotsuba was Kira.
Yes. Please tell us truthfully.
A-All right. I'll tell you everything...
I was indeed detained...
I didn't think it was L,
but he did ask me about Kira...
But I'm not the Second Kira.
I'm here because he found out
I have nothing to do with Kira.
Did you see
who was detaining you?
I was blindfolded...
But, you heard his voice,
didn't you?
Only through a speaker, so...
Hey...
This is more like an interrogation
rather than an interview.
How long do you plan
on doing this?
I'm going to the restroom.
Indeed, it seems the interview
has veered off track...
Excuse me...
May I also go to the restroom?
This is tiring...
But it's going well.
I've got to try hard...
Touching her with this piece of notebook
won't return her memories...
But at least now,
Misa can see me again...
W-What is this-?! A monster-?
Misa, you're in a dangerous situation.
The people from Yotsuba may kill you.
I came to tell you that.
Calm down and listen to me.
Calm down?
This monster looks like
it's going to kill me!
I am your ally.
My...ally?
I wonder if Misa-Misa is all right...
We should have at least wired her!
It's just as I thought...
It's definitely a different person...
The Kira before and after
I was detained...are clearly different.
The current Kira
is killing every criminal...
as soon as they've had their crime
broadcasted, regardless of the situation...
The previous Kira
would never punish...
those who didn't have
any intention to kill,
those who killed by accident, or those
with extenuating circumstances...
If I were Kira,
that's what I would do...
The original Kira's
criteria for killing...
are disturbingly close
to my own thoughts...
What am I thinking?
I'm not Kira.
There must be something wrong with me
if I'm comparing myself to Kira...
Light Yagami is Kira.
What is Light doing now-?
What are you?
I know you're not a stalker,
but you don't look human at all...
Of course. I'm a Shinigami.
Misa, we once worked together.
I don't know what
you're talking about...
You met me? Light is Kira-?
The Death Note...
If you write a person's name in it,
that person dies...
With that notebook,
Light Yagami punished criminals
and became known as Kira.
And you had the same...no,
greater power than Kira.
With that power you managed
to get close to Light Yagami.
Light is Kira...
and I'm the Second Kira?
That's right...
No, more correctly, you were.
This should all be going
according to Light's plan.
So Ryuzaki's right!
Misa...do you still love Light
more than anything?
Shinigami, you really are
the real thing.
You know everything about me.
I'll believe everything you say...
Yes... I love him...more than anything.
Besides, it's really awesome
that Light and I were both Kira.
I believe you...
You haven't changed at all, Misa...
Those feelings towards Light will
probably never change, will they?
I now believe that you'll find
happiness by staying with Light.
Thank you, Shinigami.
It's Rem.
The current Kira is a crooked
and pathetic human.
You don't know what he'll do.
Be careful.
Be careful of
the other Yotsuba men, as well.
Trust Light and let him do
whatever he feels necessary.
All right, I just have to act normal, right?
That's right.
When you go back to the interview,
you should be able to tell who's Kira.
Do not trust him..
Sorry I took so long in the restroom.
I fixed up my makeup.
Listen, when you return, the man
who's sitting in front of me is Kira.
Rem...
The person in front of Rem is Kira...
Higuchi is Kira
That's horrible...
Misa-Misa sure is late...
They're back!
Hey!
I am so tired.
Hey...
How was it?
Yotsuba hired Misa
to appear in their ads.
I see. That's great.
Once I told them
my cell phone number,
I got asked out
by three of the seven already.
What-?
I just have to accept
and investigate them, right?
It's exactly as planned.
No, the plan has been canceled.
Huh?
Why? It's been going so well...
You'll be in danger if we do this.
I won't stop you from appearing
in any of their commercials,
but from now on, deny that you were
suspected of being the Second Kira
and that you were
detained by L.
Mogi will be your bodyguard...
and you will just be
an entertainer.
If that's what you say,
then that's what I'll do...
Well, I'm tired and tomorrow's shoot
is early in the morning,
so I'm going to bed.
Thank you for worrying
about me, Light...
But I've thought of a good plan...
I'm sure to be of help to you...
Light, want to come to bed
with me?
What are you talking about, Misa?
I understand... That's for after
we catch Kira, isn't it?
You don't have to be shy, Light.
You do not have to be shy, Light.
I'm not being shy.
Why are you answering
so seriously, Light?
Cut-!
That's good!
Good work.
Good work...
Good work, Misa-Misa!
I can use the restroom
in this hospital, right?
Yes!
Medical College
Hospital
Go right ahead!
Then wait for me a moment.
Yes...
Good work, Senpai.
Wow-! Nori, you look good
in that nurse outfit-!
You think so-?
To-oh Women's Medical Center
It went well.
Whoa...
Just as I expected, an amazing car.
If you think like it,
I'll let you ride it any time...
or, I'll buy you one.
By the way, that nurse's outfit
is pretty nice, Misa.
You like it?
You sure took long.
Where's Misa?!
She's on a date.
Damn it-!
Kyosuke Higuchi...
- He's the persistent dirty old man...
- Misa, you're really my type.
who's been sending text messages...
- ever since that party.
- Hey Higuchi! Quit hogging her!
It's horrible that this guy is Kira...
Misa, shall we get something to eat?
Don't take me anywhere weird, okay?
Well, even if you try something...
It's all right because I can kill people.
What are you thinking, Misa?
Is this what Light Yagami
wants you to do?
No, is Misa just saying
that she wants me to kill Higuchi,
if something happens?
That's a funny thing to say, Misa.
You can kill people?
It's true. Because I'm...
the Second Kira.
It can't be...
Even if this girl was the Second Kira
in the past, she can't be right now.
She shouldn't have
any memory of it...
What's going on?
Misa, it's all right,
you don't have to make up things
like that to protect yourself.
I'm actually quite the gentleman.
Well, I don't really feel like
proving I'm the Second Kira
to anyone other than Kira...
You'll only show Kira?
What do you mean?
It's my dream to become Kira's bride.
I know Kira needs me by his side.
If she's the Second Kira...
then it's clear from the Sakura TV incident
that she has the Shinigami eyes...
If it is true,
I have to have her by my side...
I'll test her...
Well then, I'm Kira, so...
Marry me, Misa!
Really?!
Y-Yeah...
Really.
What-? Then prove it!
Let's show each other the proof!
That's impossible.
It would be risky to show how I kill.
You think so?
I would show someone
if they might be Kira.
Nothing would happen
if I didn't.
Then kill someone.
I may be Kira.
Fine. But I only kill bad people.
That's right. A bad person, huh-?
Ginzo Kaneboshi...
He's the president of a major
consumer financing company.
He's a crook who's famous
for his cruel collection methods.
Sometimes, he makes people
pay with their insurance money.
How about him?
Can you immediately check
if he died?
I can tell if I make a phone call.
Then turn around for a moment.
Misa...
I have to kill Ginzo Kaneboshi, don't l-?
Then Higuchi will trust you...
Fine.
Ginzo Kaneboshi
All right. He should be dead now.
This is Higuchi from Yotsuba.
Sorry! Our president just collapsed
and stopped breathing... Call back later!
See-?
She killed a person that
I chose, right here...
It would have been impossible
unless she had the powers-!
It's decided!
Then if I'm Kira,
you'll marry me, right?!
W-Why are you getting
so serious all of a sudden-?
Because I'm Kira.
Then prove it.
I can't kill until I go home.
You understand.
Yeah...then it's no good.
It might be a scheme
to lure me into your house.
Oh, I know.
Then stop killing criminals.
If you're Kira,
I'm sure you can do it.
Then begin killing when I tell you to.
Then I'll believe you.
Killing criminals...is something
that only Kira could do.
I see. That's a good idea.
All right.
I'm Kira, so in order
to make you trust me,
I'm going to stop
killing criminals starting now.
And when you know I'm Kira,
we'll get married!
And so...
Higuchi is Kira.
Now we'll know Kira's identity
and the killings that have been
bothering the Chief, will stop-!
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
It's been three days
since I stopped killing criminals.
That should be good enough.
Now, If I marry Misa Amane,
the Second Kira,
I'll have the Shinigami eyes.
And I'll control everything Yotsuba has!