Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change the dream into reality
The ending that everybody wants.
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal world.
My studious son is looking at
a magazine like that...
Light, it's time for dinner...
I'll solve equations with my right hand...
And write names with my left.
I'll take a potato chip...
And eat it!
The witness to my alibi is L himself.
Are you sure, Ryuk?
Yeah. Nobody's following you.
G-Give it to me quickly.
My withdrawal symptoms...
You're not just saying that
so I'll give you an apple, right?
Hey, hey!
I've flown around and checked
a hundred-meter radius around you.
I'm sure.
But there was the news report about
Interpol dispatching of 1,500 investigators...
It's a bluff, of course.
You said it yourself.
If it were real, they would sneak in
and investigate secretly.
All right, Ryuk. I'll buy you an apple.
All right!
Thank you very much.
Light! Quickly, quickly.
You really are a slave driver...
You had me search for cameras...
And made me give up
eating apples in the house.
Be sure to eat the core as well.
In the end, I'll really write your name
in my Death Note, and kill ya!
Is this any time to be laughing?
That's right. There's just one thing left
to top everything off.
Ryuzaki...
Yes?
About the purse-snatcher and embezzler's
heart attacks two days ago...
That happened before my family
had any knowledge of it.
Have they been cleared?
I suppose you're right...
Even though Kira can control
the time of death,
I don't think that there's any way
he could set up his victims without
watching that broadca...!
Your son has come home again.
So, you're gonna shut up and act like
you're studying again, huh?
I already have an idea of
where all the cameras are.
But I was only able to kill
a purse-snatcher and an embezzler
Tayoshi Murao
Suspect: Tayoshi Murao
They've committed really minor crimes
compared to those I've killed until now.
Are you going to watch TV?
I killed criminals whose names
and faces were broadcast
when I didn't have access
to TV or the internet.
But there still is a chance
that I'll be suspected because
only minor criminals die
when I don't have any information...
In other words...
If I also kill minor criminals
being broadcast when I watch TV...
I won't call attention to myself.
Also, when I go out...
regardless of the severity
of the crime...
I should remember the names
of criminals broadcast...
And kill them...at random times...
with the piece of the Death Note
I left in my wallet.
Now my measures against
the cameras are perfect.
During these past few days...
I have checked our tapes
and video footage many times.
I've come to a decision.
Among the Kitamura and
Yagami households...
No one is suspicious.
I shall remove the cameras
and wiretaps.
So, in the end the culprit
wasn't here, huh?
Don't lower your guard!
We're going to narrow down
our possibilities once more.
Please don't get the wrong idea...
I just meant that there wasn't
anyone suspicious
from what I could see
from our footage.
Huh?
Even if Kira is among them,
he wouldn't give himself away.
No, it means that he was killing criminals
as usual, without showing it.
Then you believe that one of them
might be Kira?
I'd say it's...
A five-percent chance.
Kira was still killing people even while
the surveillance cameras were in place...
I don't know how he did it.
But even if he is able to kill people
by wishing death upon them...
if he were a normal person,
he would have behaved differently
or at least changed his facial expression
when committing the murders...
Kira is not among them.
Most people would conclude that.
But... If Kira is one of them...
His psyche has reached
a god-like level.
Judging sinners without
changing his expression.
I want to believe that Kira
doesn't really exist...
that this is really divine judgement.
But it's absurd to think that God would
need a person's face and name to kill.
But this isn't divine judgement
by God.
It's the actions of someone childish
who thinks he's God.
That's what this is.
The mass murderer known
as Kira does exist.
And I will catch him.
But I don't think that Kira will
expose himself
even if I keep these cameras in place...
What should I do?
It would be best to get him to
tell me himself that he's Kira,
and have him
show me how he kills...
But there's no way I can...
Hey, Light. The cameras
really have been removed!
All of them, all of them!
Light... Are you listening?
Hey, Light.
Oh, I see.
The wiretaps might still be here.
I'm no longer a suspect.
It's all happened as I'd planned.
But L will probably continue to chase Kira.
And if he's still using the Japanese police...
My father will be among
those being used.
If that's the case...
I'll use my father to find
out L's identity so I can...
eliminate him...
If I just get rid of L...
Kira will be one step closer
to becoming the god of the new world.
Light, hurry up.
Do your best!
Good luck, Light!
Really, you're making such
a big fuss over this.
I'll be going.
It sure feels good, now that we know
that there aren't any wiretaps.
Well, it's nice to know that
one cause of stress is gone before my test.
2007 Test Center for
University Admissions
To-oh University Test
Once I start college, I'll have more time
to operate as Kira and search for L.
You there! The test will start
in ten minutes! Hurry up!
I was planning on going in
three minutes before the test
because I didn't want to wait
in the classroom...
I sure got here early.
That's some confidence you've got.
You may begin.
You there... Number 162...
Sit in your seat properly!
There's been quite
a lot of Shinigami...
looking real hard into
the human world lately.
What's with that?
It seems that Ryuk has turned
into some human's pet.
W-What in the world is he thinking-?
Really. He's a disgrace to
all Shinigami.
No, I'm talking about the human
who's keeping him.
Ryuk's probably not a very cute pet.
Well, yeah.
So what kind of human's keeping him?
Is it a woman? A man?
Who knows...
I'll go take a peek as well...
Oh well...
2007 To-Oh University Entrance Ceremony
So you're a college student
now, huh, Light?
My heart's filled with emotion.
Now for our freshman address.
And our freshman representative,
Light Yagami.
Yes.
Oh, wow.
Likewise, freshman representative,
Hideki Ryuga.
Oh! Yeah...
Hideki Ryuga, the pop idol?!
Couldn't be... There's no way he's smart
enough to enter To-oh.
Ah... You're right. He doesn't even
look anything like him.
I heard I was going to be giving
the address with someone else, but...
I never thought it was going to be him.
He's the guy who was sitting weird
behind me on the first day of the Exams.
He completely stood out...
from everyone else.
Life springs renewed
in the breath of Spring...
The person who scored highest on
the test is supposed to do this, right?
That just means that there were
two top scorers this year...
I heard they both
scored 100% in all subjects.
Seriously?
I guess there really are people like that.
I definitely like the guy on the right!
What-?! Kyoko, you're weird.
Most people would choose
the one on the left.
But those two sure are different...
Yeah...
One looks like a brilliant genius
from a sheltered family.
The other...
Life springs renewed
in the breath of Spring...
Seems wild... Or at least very weird...
Is that what people would call a genius?
He's doing the address...
for the To-oh entrance ceremony
dressed like that.
He is either not taking this seriously
or an idiot.
Thank you very much...
Hideki Ryuga.
Yagami...
You are the son of Soichiro Yagami,
Detective Superintendent of the NPA.
You have a sense of justice which
rivals that of your respect for your father.
Who is this guy?
You also aim to become
a police official...
and have helped the police to
solve several cases in the past.
You're now showing great interest
in the Kira case.
I have faith in your sense of
justice and abilities,
and if you swear not to tell anyone,
I'll tell you something very important
concerning the Kira case.
What is this all of a sudden?
Should I just ignore him?
But what is this important information
concerning the Kira case...
I won't tell anyone. What is it?
I'm L.
I-It couldn't be!
What is he talking about?!
There's no way that
L would say that he's L.
I thought he was a strange guy,
but is he really that weird?
T-This isn't good.
Don't be shocked.
If he really is L...
I have to act naturally,
how Soichiro Yagami's son Light would act.
If you truly are who you say you are,
I respect and admire you.
Thank you...
I revealed myself because I think that
you can be of help in solving
the Kira case.
Light Yagami...
The probability that you are Kira
is just under five percent.
But out of everyone we were watching,
I sensed something from you.
You're too perfect.
And if you're Kira, there's nothing that
could pressure you more than this.
If this guy's really L,
he's something else.
Indeed...if he really is L.
No, Even if he isn't really L...
I...
I can't do anything to him!
If what he's saying is true, he's probably
already shown his face to my father.
If he dies as soon as he reveals
himself to me,
then suspicion will immediately
fall onto me.
And he's using an obvious
alias like Hideki Ryuga.
If his name really isn't Hideki Ryuga
and I try to kill him by writing
his name in the Death Note...
Hideki Ryuga
The pop idol Ryuga's face will pop up
in my head whether I want it to or not...
and he may die instead...
But he won't die and will
surmise that I'm Kira.
Is he really L-?
Also, does he suspect that I'm Kira?
I don't know how much he knows,
but I'm sure he suspects me.
There's no other reason for him to
tell Soichiro Yagami's son that he's L.
Does this mean that
he's still focusing on
the people that
Raye Penber was investigating?
But why has L approached
me directly-?
Not now...
It's better to keep my mind blank.
I have to keep a straight face.
He's definitely checking to see
whether I'm shocked now...
2007 To-oh University Entrance Ceremony
Light, that was an interesting
college entrance ceremony.
Yagami.
Hey, Light... He's calling you.
It was nice to meet you...
No, the pleasure was all mine...
What an amazing car...
A limousine?
Well, I'll see you around campus.
Oh, yeah.
Where is that rich kid from?
And he's even at the top of the class?
What a jerk.
Ah, welcome home,
To-oh University student!
Damn! He got me!
He got you-?
Damn it, L... I've never been
so humiliated in my life!
Say, why don't you just do
the Shinigami eye deal with me
and just kill him?
What good would that
do if this is a trap?!
If he's not really L, then that would
be just like telling L that I'm Kira!
S-Sorry...
Shinigami killing people and
humans killing people aren't the same thing.
I want to kill him no matter what it takes,
but if I do, it'll be traced back to me...
The Death Note can only kill a
person whose name I write in it...
I cannot control someone
to kill someone else.
The Death Note is a pain in the ass!
Light is usually calm,
but he's fuming now...
He's pretty annoyed.
At first, I thought that when
I found out his name,
I'd have him get in
an accident or commit suicide.
But it's no good unless
I know a hundred percent that he's L.
No. Even if I do know it's him,
it may be too late.
No matter what the cause of death,
if L dies, I'll be suspected...
I underestimated him...
I never thought that L would come up
to me and say, "I'm L!"
He just has to tell all
the suspects that he is L.
Even if he's his double...
This is a solid defense as well as
an attack against Kira.
He beat me... It was a good move...
Ryuga will play dumb and probably
continue to approach me
and manipulate me at the university...
This is great...
There's nothing to worry about.
This proves that they don't have
anything on me...
It's a contest between L and me.
It's a game of wits!
On the surface, we'll be
friendly acquaintances on campus.
In reality, we'll be investigating each other,
"Are you L?" or "Are you Kira?"
This is interesting, Ryuga.
If it's friendship you want from me,
I'll gladly accept.
I'll make you trust me...
And once I've pulled everything
out of you, I will kill you...
with my own hands!
I dreamed a dream that no one could see,
I threw away everything that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
that I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
to accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster who doesn't know solitude
Hideki Ryuga, L...
There's no way that he could profile me
with this tennis game.
He has some other goal in mind.
But even if it's just tennis, I will win!