Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change the dream into reality
The ending that everybody wants.
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal world.
What?!
There were another
23 victims yesterday?!
As soon as we began to suspect
that Kira was a student,
the timing of the killings changed as
if to contradict our theory.
Does that mean that Kira knows
what the police know?
When L discovers that the findings
from the investigation were leaked,
he's bound to search for leads on me
within the police force.
Someone's been following you
all this time.
That's a problem...
Ryuk, I'll be sure to finish him off.
In a Shinigami's eyes...
a human's name and life span
can be seen above person's face.
Shinigami can also turn the eyes
of whoever picked up their Death Note
into Shinigami eyes.
The price for a Shinigami's eyes
is half of that person's remaining life span.
So...
Light, what'll it be?
I haven't seen Ryuk around lately...
Did he really lose his Death Note
in the Human World?
The Death Note was probably picked up
by a human before he got to it.
Couldn't be...
If that happened to him, he'd have to
follow that person around
until that person dies
or the Death Note is destroyed.
Yeah.
I can't picture Ryuk
doing something so tedious.
I heard that he was
carrying two Death Notes.
Seriously?
Why would he need two?
I don't understand
what he's thinking.
In order for me to gain
the eyes of a Shinigami...
I have to offer half of my life.
Is that right?
Yeah.
What are you going to do?
Do you wanna make
a deal with me?
Ryuk.
This deal...
is out of the question.
Now listen.
I want to create an ideal,
new world free from criminals.
I also intend to reign as
the god in that world for a long time.
I would consider the deal if
it lengthened my life,
but it's not worth talking
about if it's going to shorten it.
You, of all people,
should know that.
Yeah, I just felt I should tell
you a deal like this exists.
I don't want you to complain that
I didn't tell you about this earlier.
If you didn't tell me
about this earlier?
Don't you think you're too late already?
You should have told me this
when we first met
or included this when you were writing
instructions in the Death Note...
Yeah. I guess you're right.
Even though I'm a Shinigami,
he's not frightened nor
does he try to suck up to me.
He has no problem giving me
a hard time about things like this...
Well?
Hmm?
You sure there isn't anything else you
want to tell me ahead of time?
Shinigami Ryuk...
Nope, nothing else...
Probably...
Is that so?
How disappointing.
Disappointing?
I may have seriously
considered the deal
if you offered me wings
rather than eyes.
Flying around freely in the sky
is very God-like.
It's a dream that man
has had since ancient times.
You'd stand out if you sprouted
wings and started flying around.
I'd bet you'd get arrested
by the police just for that.
Ryuk, that was a joke.
However, if I continue to
deal for eyes and wings...
I'm going to end up becoming
a real Shinigami.
That could be amusing,
don't you think?
Don't worry.
Even without all that,
you're already...
a worthy Shinigami!
The Shinigami Realm is
rotting these days.
They all live vacant lives
and only take human lives...
because they don't want to die.
No one even knows...
why we exist.
I doubt there's any reason
at all for our existence.
You're much more of
a Shinigami than they are.
Well, from what you're saying, it sounds
like I'm doing a lot more work.
But I don't want to be lumped together
with the Shinigami.
I am using this Death Note
as a human for humans.
But, I wouldn't say that the Shinigami Realm
is meaningless to humans either.
What do you mean?
Well, think about it.
Whenever a Shinigami like you
comes to the Human World
once every hundred, no,
every thousand years,
the Human World
changes greatly.
The Shinigami Realm's existence
is fearfully meaningful.
I-ls that so...?
You told me that the
Shinigami Realm is rotten.
When you return
from this world,
how about using what you've
learned here to try to change it?
Light...you may be
quite the positive thinker.
Of course, I am.
If I wasn't, I wouldn't be
trying to use
the Death Note to try to
make the world a better place.
That's it!
I've got it!
What's up?
What did you get?
How to find out the name of
the guy who was following me today.
How are you going to do it?
I'm going to use the rules of
the Death Note to my advantage.
If I write a cause of death...
I have an additional
6 minutes and 40 seconds
to record specific conditions
and time of death.
I wonder how free I can
be with these conditions?
I'm going to test it out.
The Following Morning
Yes, it's me.
Another six inmates...
Heart attacks?!
It's Kira.
What?
Three exhibited bizarre behavior
before they died?!
What do you mean?!
They didn't just die from
simple heart attacks?
Well, they died of heart attacks,
but before one of them died...
he drew a strange picture
on the wall with blood from his finger.
Another left a letter that doesn't seem
like a will or anything meaningful.
The third escaped just to go
to the employees' bathroom.
Watari, what is it?
More victims, but their circumstances
are unlike those we've had before.
Unlike those before?
I shall send you an image of
the picture and letter left at the scene.
If you could.
A note describing a fear of Kira.
This can be taken as
something a criminal might do, but...
Kira can control the time of death.
If he can control actions
right before death as well...
that would mean that...
Chief!
It's about these current victims.
Don't let the media know anything
aside from the fact that
they died of heart attacks.
It's possible that Kira
was performing some kind of test.
If that's the case, we'd only
be giving him the answer.
I see...
I-I understand.
Performing tests on criminals?
That's horrible...
He's playing with peoples' lives
as if this is a game.
This is unforgivable!
If Kira is using criminals
as test subjects...
What is he trying to achieve?
Look at this, Ryuk.
The results of yesterday's test have
already been input into Dad's computer.
Keito Nawarami: Kidnapping Murder
Kyu Nishida: Insurance Fraud Murder
The results are just as I expected.
The Death Note will work
for what I have in mind.
What do you mean by that?
One escaped...
and went to the bathroom
I had designated in the Death Note.
Tamiki: Heart attack,
escapes from cell.
Dies 6 p.m.
Masaaki: Heart attack,
draws symbol on wall
Another drew the same picture
I had drawn in the Death Note.
Yet another wrote the same letter
I had written in the Death Note.
Lord have mercy
Do what I can,
I'll either be
hanged or you
know it, killed
by Kira. I know
about him. He's
going to get me.
These three did exactly what I wanted.
I purposely wrote very difficult tasks
for the other three.
Yuzo Fura: Dies
in front of the
Eiffel Tower France,
today at 6 p.m.
The first was to "Die in front of the
Eiffel Tower in an hour."
It's physically impossible to go from
a prison in Japan to France in an hour.
So this never happened and ended
as just a regular heart attack.
Kabeoka: Heart Attack
Draws exact image
of L's face on prison wall
Dies at 6 p.m.
The next was to "draw a picture of L's face
on the prison wall," but...
One can't draw the faces...
of people they don't know.
I see.
Kabeoka: Heart Attack
Draws exact image of
L's face on prison wall
Dies at 6 p.m.
Shinshiro Yamamae: Heart Attack
Writes a note stating "I know that L is
suspicious of the Japanese police."
Dies at 6 p.m.
For the final one,
I specified that he would write...
Dies at 6 p.m.
a note that would read, "I know L is
suspicious of the Japanese police."
I thought this one might work,
but it didn't happen.
Which means that people can't write
about things they don't know or things
they couldn't come up with on their own.
In short, it means that even the
Death Note can't do the impossible.
But as long as it's something
the person is realistically likely to do,
I can control them as much as
I want before he dies.
You've figured that out...
But what are you trying to do, Light?
L and the police will never
figure out my true goal.
The great detective
is probably trying
to decipher the picture and
the letter those criminals left.
It's an absolutely
meaningless dying message.
If Kira used those criminals for a test,
he's about to start something.
If he moves now,
there is the chance that...
the FBI will notice someone
acting suspiciously.
But if he has a different goal in mind...
the letter and picture might
be some kind of message...
Is this it?
L  D O  Y O U  K N O W
Well... It's time for the real thing.
The real thing?
Yesterday on the news...
There was a drug addict who tried
to rob a bank,
Wanted Criminal
Kiichiro Osoreda
but wasn't able to steal any money.
He attacked civilians and ran away.
I'll use him.
It's last minute, but I'm sure
I can find someone...
I'll try to ask out several people.
Ask out...several people?
Yeah.
Ryuk, I may not look it,
but I'm pretty popular.
Hello? Huh, Light?
Good morning...
He's still following me, isn't he?
That's perfect.
If I don't have my stalker,
there would be no point in what
I'm going to do next.
Light!
- A date?
- Yeah.
It's a date,
no matter how you look at it.
Even to my stalker.
It's no normal date, is it?
You said you found a way
to find out your stalker's name, but...
What do you plan to do?
Huh? Ryuk, didn't you see
what I wrote in the Death Note?
Nah. It would be boring to peek.
Then just be patient and
watch what happens.
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
No, not at all!
Anyway, I haven't been to
Space Land since junior high!
I'm so excited!
And I get to be alone with you!
Y-Yeah.
On weekdays, he only goes
to school and his prep courses.
An occasional date on his days off.
He's pretty normal.
No, he's a serious
high school student.
Chief Yagami's son, Light.
I have no reason to suspect him.
At any rate...
I'll finish my surveillance
of him today.
Light...
Didn't you say that you weren't going out
until entrance exams were over?
Yeah, but I did score number one
in the practice exams.
You're awful!
It's him! He's here!
Aside from him,
there are seven passengers.
Everything will go smoothly.
Huh?
I'm taking control of this bus!
A bus jacking!
At a time like this?
Don't make a fuss!
I'll kill anyone that moves.
Driver, you know the phone number
for Space Land's offices, don't you?
Call them!
Y-Yes.
T-This is Sasaki, the driver of
bus number 174!
Tell them what's happening!
A man with a gun has
bus jacked us!
Give me that.
You hear that? Listen carefully.
Bring Space Land's profits from yesterday
to two bus stops away from there.
Have a woman bring it
by car alone!
Do it before this bus gets there!
If you try anything funny...
or call the police,
I'll kill all the passengers one by one!
Yuri, don't worry.
I'll look for the chance to grab his hand...
that's holding the pistol.
That's dangerous. Don't do it.
If it comes to that, I'll do it.
It's all right.
We don't have to pass notes.
As long as we whisper, he won't hear us
over the sound of the bus.
Do you have proof that
you're not his accomplice?
A-Accomplice?
It's pretty common.
The culprit pretends he's alone
and just in case...
he'll leave someone to
keep watch in the back.
What's wrong?
No...you really think so...?
I-I have no choice.
There is no way that
Light Yagami can be Kira.
Kira could kill the culprit
with a heart attack.
This is my proof.
Take a look.
FBI?!
I see, L's using the FBI to investigate
those connected to Japan's police force!
His name is...
Raye Penber.
I trust you.
I won't ask why an FBI agent
is on this bus with us.
- Do you have a gun?
- Yes, I do.
So if something happens,
I can rely on you, right?
Yes.
Shut up!
Do you want to die?!
That man was on the
Japanese news two days ago.
He's a drug addict who tried
to rob a bank,
killed three civilians,
and ran away.
He's very dangerous.
It'll all right.
He'll never shoot at us.
Oh!
Hey, you! Don't move.
What's that piece of paper?
Hey you!
You were planning something back here
with notes, weren't you?
Damn!
If he sees that note from earlier...
He'll discover that Light was planning
to jump him when he had the chance!
Heh. Plans for a date?
How stupid.
All right!
W-Who the hell are you?!
You in the back?
W-What are you trying to pull?
H-How long were you
hiding back there?!
Huh? You mean me?
You can see me right now?
D-Don't move!
I-I'll shoot!
You monster!
This isn't good!
He's hallucinating!
Everyone, get down!
Oh, I get it!
That note that Light just dropped...
was cut out of the Death Note.
So he has this guy touch the note
and now, only he can see me.
That's so smart.
D-Don't come near me!
Sorry, pal.
I'm a Shinigami,
so that's not gonna kill me.
"Anyone who touches the Death Note
will be able to see me..."
"I'm always hovering behind you."
"Shinigami can't die from gunshots..."
That's all stuff I've told Light...
Pretty impressive,
he used his skills.
It's not surprising he's the
top exam scorer nationwide...
He even used this bus jacking to get the
name of the guy who was following him...
without much hassle.
Stop the bus and open the door.
Space Land
Exactly 11:45.
Everything went as planned...
Wanted Criminal
Kiichiro Osoreda, Accidental death...
At 11:31 a.m., he will get on
a bus heading to Space Land
from the bus stop near
the eastern entrance of the park.
He will enter with a gun,
but will see a phantom from another
world and fires all his bullets at it.
Then, he will flee from the bus...
Immediately afterwards, at 11:45
the same day, he will die in an accident.
The Death Note never fails.
You're next, Raye Penber.
I dreamed a dream that no one could see,
I threw away everything that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
that I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
to accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster who doesn't know solitude
It's just as I thought.
He doesn't suspected me at all.
Please keep what is about to happen
a secret between the eight of us.
The remaining agents will
all die of heart attacks.
Farewell, Raye Penber.