Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
December 2007
What did you say, Roger?!
Say it again!
L is dead.
Dead?! Why?
Did Kira kill him?
Is that it?
Probably...
He said that he would get Kira
executed... and was killed...!
Is that what you're saying?!
Mello...
If you can't beat the game...
If you can't solve the puzzle...
You're nothing but a loser.
Me or Near?
So which one of us did L...?
Neither one of you yet...
He can't choose...if he's dead.
Mello...Near...
How about the both of you
work together...
Sure. Sounds good.
That's impossible, Roger.
You know that Near and
I don't get along.
We've always competed
against each other...
Always...
It's fine, Roger.
Near should succeed L.
Unlike me, Near will...
solve this unemotionally,
like a puzzle.
I'm leaving...this institution.
Mello!
I'm almost fifteen, anyway.
I'll live my life my own way.
A police officer who happened to be
nearby when Higuchi was arrested...
March 5, 2012
heard that if you write
the name of someone you know in
the notebook, that person will die.
Are you saying that's what
the notebook of death is?
Yes. The Japanese police
should have it right now.
A young man
named Near
presents
evidence
on the
Kira case
which he has
gathered
by himself
over the
last three
years.
He meets
with the
president
accompanied
by the
director
of the FBI.
Mr. President, the current L is one
that the Japanese police have
created to avoid confusion.
L is dead.
Director Mason... Who is he-?
Well...
He is, shall we say...
L's true successor.
The United
States of
America...
creates their own
investigation team
independent of L
to go after Kira.
The SPK (Special
Provision for Kira)
is composed of
hand-picked FBI
and CIA agents
along with Near.
But...
It's impossible to censor
the internet and...
the Kira case has slowed to
a dead-end lately...
Maybe those who show people
they want killed on the internet
should be killed.
But Kira gets some of his information
from the internet,
so he won't kill them.
Matsu, your idea is full
of contradictions.
If only people wouldn't do bad things...
Or rather...the world's become
a good place for the innocent.
I suppose there are people
who might believe that.
Look who's talking.
No...Soon everyone will
think in that way...
Are you talking about that again?
Stop it...
Dear, Light.
I'm home...
Welcome back!
Welcome home, Sayu.
Light, Misa.
It's unusual for both of
you to be here. Welcome.
Pardon the intrusion.
Mr. Matsuda, wasn't it-?
Oh, yes!
It's been a while.
Thank you for taking care
of my father.
S-Sayu...
Y-You've grown up and
you're so pretty...
When I last saw you,
you were like this...
Matsu's bright red!
Huh? No way...
There's no way I'm letting
Sayu marry a detective.
Huh?
That's right. I definitely
don't want that.
What? No way!
I never even got to propose...
or even confess that I love her...
Mom and Dad.
- Mo...?
- Dad?!
Well... I think you're wonderful.
What-? R-Really, Sayu?
Yes. I might have considered
going out with you
if you were a little younger.
You've sure learned how to talk.
Really. She's more mature
than Matsu.
But Light,
you haven't changed one bit
and you're as wonderful
as when I first met you.
Light, you've already found a career...
So stop just living together in secret
and get married already.
That sounds good...!
What an unfortunate
and heart-warming family...
How interesting!
What is it, Aizawa?
Yes.
Yes. Yes. All right.
Matsuda, Light, come with me.
A kidnapping-?
Who kidnapped whom?
Director Takimura of the NPA...
I don't know by whom.
Damn! As if the current situation
with the Kira case wasn't enough...
Deputy Director
Are you sure?
I got the phone call at 6:12.
45 minutes ago.
We determined it was from
the director's cell phone.
Did the kidnappers make
any demands?
Well...
They wanted to trade the director...
for the killer notebook...
Who-? For what purpose-?
Do you suppose it's Kira?
Well, if the existence of
the Death Note was leaked,
countless people would want it...
Dad, how much does
the director know?
We tried to keep the knowledge
of the notebook within our group.
That's right. I never discussed it
with the director.
The existence of the Death Note...
Someone knows that the NPA
has it and they've come to take it...
Notify every bureau of the NPA only
about the director's kidnapping.
Yes.
Is it a call from the culprit?!
No. There's someone who wants
to meet Director Takimura.
What?
I'm John MacEnrow,
an agent with the FBI.
Of course, this is an alias.
Since what I am doing concerns Kira.
Please forgive me.
Kira...
The Director is out
at the moment.
If it's all right, I'll listen to what
you have to say.
Well, that's fine.
Excuse me for going straight
to the point,
but the Japanese police
are unreliable.
In order to solve the Kira case,
we want you to hand over
the notebook to our country...
So it was the FBI!
Where have you taken
our director?!
W-What are you talking about?
Don't act like
you don't know!
This is a brazen
criminal offense!
What would we gain by hiding
the director of the Japan's NPA-?
Then how do you know...
- about the notebook?!
- What's going on?
It seems that the director of the NPA
has been kidnapped by someone.
Someone who wants
the notebook...
Commander Rester.
Hmm?
Suggest to him that we'd like to help
rescue the director
and apprehend the culprit.
We'll take the notebook when
we have the chance.
All right.
Can you hear me?
This is headquarters.
These are your orders.
Did he say anything?
The Japanese police have begun
to wimp out on Kira.
It seems that the only ones
who are working with L are...
Soichiro Yagami, Kanzo Mogi,
and Touta Matsuda.
Isn't that right?
Yeah...
There was another called Ukita,
but he died...
Even though you were
the director of the NPA...
you didn't know about
the notebook?
The Japanese police really suck.
The highest-ranking of the three
is Yagami,
who was the chief detective
of the task force, right?
Yeah...
I think there are two notebooks.
Kira has one...
The NPA has the other.
We'll take both.
There's no mistake if
Mello says so.
Has he ever been wrong since
he joined us a year and a half ago?
But why is the guy who brought us
the head of a mafia boss Kira couldn't kill...
so fixated on the notebook?
I don't just want the notebook.
I want to kill everyone
who stands in my way...
And be number one!
By whatever means necessary,
before Near does...
B-Boss!
What is it? Be quiet.
Sorry. Eddie and I were
just talking...and
Takimura hung himself
with his necktie-!
You idiot!
What good is a dead hostage?!
No, that's fine.
If Kira is responsible for this...
He can't touch us since
he doesn't know our names or faces.
Thus he went after Takimura.
Which means...
Kira is someone who knows
about this kidnapping...
What are you going to do, Mello?
Kidnap Soichiro Yagami's daughter,
Sayu Yagami next.
There are still no clues about...
the director or the kidnappers...
Aside from that,
why haven't they said anything
since they kidnapped him?
Light, there's no mistake
that the real name
of the FBI agent who calls himself
John MacEnrow, is really Larry Conners.
Is that so? Thank goodness.
He's a real agent...
The director of the FBI also said
that he would help us
rescue director Takimura.
I think we can trust him.
The director should
already be dead...
Why don't they say anything?
Would they give up on
the deal just because he died?
I didn't think we were dealing
with such weaklings...
Dad... No, everyone here
should be careful.
The director may not know
about the notebook,
but he knows who was
working with L.
If that gets out, there's a chance...
- that they'll come after us-
- Light!
I'll be a good girl tonight and
go to sleep alone, okay?
Yeah, good night.
Good night-!
Then I'll stay here...
We're not the only ones in danger.
Our families and...
The director's cell phone...
It's from the kidnappers!
Aizawa!
Yes, tracing!
This is Yagami.
Mr. Deputy Director-?
About the trade of the director
for the notebook...
It's canceled.
Takimura is dead.
What?!
W-Why you...
However, it's only canceled
with respect to the director.
We'll now trade the notebook...
for Sayu Yagami.
You're the deputy director
of the NPA.
It would be ridiculous to expect
you not to tell the police.
But I want you to move
by yourself.
I'll kill your daughter if I see
the police do anything big.
That's right...
as swiftly as we killed the director,
I'll send you a picture of
Takimura's corpse.
Take a good look.
I'll contact you tomorrow.
H-Hey!
They got me...
They used the death of the director
as an opportunity to get Sayu...
Light, things have gotten
interesting again.
Sir...
Why would they
go this far-?
Damn...!
Yagami
Yes, yes.
Dear, you never call from
your work phone...
Huh? Sayu?
Who knows-?
Come to think of it, she's late.
Sayu...
Big Brother
Dad, are you all right?
I think that it was Kira
who killed the director,
not the kidnappers.
- Huh?
- What?!
He probably doesn't want
the notebook to be passed to criminals.
Kira is acting as an icon of justice,
so he doesn't want the notebook
to fall into criminal hands.
If Kira killed the director...
it's possible that he
has methods to obtain information
within the police department.
It's best if we were
the only ones to investigate.
If not...
Kira will try to kill
the hostage again.
That's right.
Near.
The kidnapped director of
the Japanese NPA was killed.
By whom?
By the kidnappers...
It would be interesting
if it was Kira.
That's true...
They can't get the notebook
if their hostage is dead.
Also, if it was Kira...
I can narrow down the suspects.
By the way, Commander Rester...
Have you tracked his whereabouts?
Well... We're sure that he left the
institution 4 years ago as you said,
but we don't know anything
else after that.
Then it's decided.
Mello...You always overlook
the most important things
because you become too emotional.
Or maybe you're not involved
in this case at all?
How could you leave your picture
at the orphanage?
This is Yagami.
Your daughter has finally
arrived here.
Here?
You have a pretty good idea
of where this is, don't you?
We'll do the exchange here.
At any rate, bring the notebook
to Los Angeles,
by yourself in two days.
I won't do the exchange unless
I make sure my daughter's safe.
Let me hear her voice!
All right. All right.
I'll send you another picture.
Sayu!
Sir, we've narrowed them
down to Fifth Street in Los Angeles.
The TV show on in the background...
is definitely being
broadcast right now.
They showed us that on purpose
to let us know she's all right...
T-Thank goodness...
At least, she's alive...
I'm taking the notebook
to Los Angeles.
As the deputy director of the NPA
and as Sayu Yagami's father!
I'll make all the decisions
and take full responsibility!
Dad! We have to make a plan first.
That's right, Deputy Director.
But I have to be in Los Angeles
within two days...
We have no time...
So you're saying that it was Kira
who killed Takimura,
not the kidnappers?
I'm just saying that
it's a possibility.
If so, it means Kira gained information
from the Japanese police...
Yes?
This is L.
It's L...the current one.
Director, I've heard what
Agent John MacEnrow...
no, Larry Conners had to say
from Deputy Director Yagami.
Will you help us with NPA Director
Takimura's murder investigation?
Well...
Pass me the phone...
Nice to meet you, L Number Two.
Number Two?
What do you mean by that?
Who are you?
It's useless to try and hide it.
We are a new organization,
the SPK,
established to capture Kira
without the help of L.
Seven of our top members
know of L's death.
L's death-? From whom-?
From where-?
And I am at the center of the SPK...
I guess I would be... N.
N-? Is he joking?
But...what's...
this strange feeling?
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
Damn! What's going on?!
I checked the crew of today's
flight ahead of time.
There wasn't anyone suspicious.
I can still make it.
At this rate, is my only option
to kill...Sayu?