Easy easy banzai Easy easy banzai
Easy easy banzai Human
Wanna get them mad? Get them mad?
Get them mad? People
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
(play a trick on resentment Who's down?)
What's up? Full of causes for concern
Crime won't disappear Forever
Hey Hey! A hymn to humanity
Love has gone People, are you worried?
Hey Hey! Subservient People!!
WHAT'S UP, PEOPLE?!!
Are you worried?
Let's begin our meeting.
Only seven of the eight are present.
That means that...
They probably killed one of them.
To further the growth of
the Yotsuba Group...
who should we kill?
See? It's like I said.
This is bad.
If this keeps up...
Before that, we have several topics
which we should discuss.
The first is Hatori's death.
That couldn't be helped.
To be honest,
I'm relieved that he's dead.
Kira has clearly shown
what'll happen
to whoever tries
to leave these meetings.
Yeah...
I think we all know what
Hatori's death means.
Take it to heart.
Next, Eraldo Coil's report...
One of their partners just died.
Is that it?!
Five million dollars.
Just for this report, huh?
He hasn't found anything
important about L,
like his face and name.
Is this Coil really of any use?
Well, wait.
At the end of this report...
Coil warns us that we shouldn't
take L's existence lightly.
It says, "lf you continue with your
current pace of killing..."
"for Yotsuba's benefit...
every week on Fridays and Saturdays..."
"L could possibly connect
you with Kira."
It's impressive that Coil has
figured out what we've been doing.
At any rate, we should stop killing...
every weekend.
This is amazing.
It's like they're confessing.
Yeah.
As long as we have this video,
we could probably arrest
all seven of them.
This is definitely bad...
Kira isn't very flexible either.
It would be nice if he killed
at various times during the week.
The fact that Coil noticed this,
makes it dangerous to
continue killing at our current pace.
From now on,
we should be even more careful
and make sure nobody ever notices.
Now, on to the main topic.
Who shall we kill?
We must stop E.L.F. Insurance
from expanding their business
into the Japan market.
Yotsuba and many other companies'
clients will be swept away.
Agreed.
So, is it all right for these people
from E.L.F. to die by accidental deaths?
No objections.
What is this?
How can they do this so easily?
Another person is Santaro Zenzai,
a member of the Kugisawa Group.
He's protesting Yotsuba's plans
for the resort development.
Zenzai suffers from
high blood pressure.
So...it is possible to have him
die of a stroke at a designated time.
Is this all right?
No objections.
Kira...death by accident...
death by disease...
designated time of deaths.
It's as we thought.
There's no mistake.
No. Unfortunately, we can only say that
after those people they named die.
As long as we continue to monitor
what these seven say at their meetings,
their actions, and whether
the people they name die...
we'll definitely catch Kira.
Ryuzaki!
What is it?
Both of you in unison...
I can't go along with your idea!
It's wrong!
Yes!
Here it comes...
You seem to plan on catching Kira
by allowing these seven to
continue to kill, but I can't let them!
That's right. It's apparent that
these seven are committing murder!
Can't we prove it's them by
Matsuda's testimony and this footage?
This is problematic.
If we caught them now,
everything we've done until
now will go to waste.
So the E.L.F. will be three weeks later.
We'll ask Kira to have Zenzai
killed this weekend.
How about it?
No objections.
If it's this weekend,
there's not much time left!
Light, you know the cell phone numbers
of those seven, right?
Yeah.
Any one of them will do.
I'm going to call one of those seven
and stop the killing!
Please wait.
If we do that just three days
after Aiber's made contact with them,
we'll arouse suspicion that
our investigation is catching up to them.
It's also highly unlikely
that we won't be able to
figure out who Kira is.
We came this far,
but we'll have to start back
at the beginning.
In order to catch Kira...
we need proof.
Ryuzaki.
If Kira is among these seven,
isn't it fair to assume that
if we call one of them...
there's a one in seven chance that
that person is Kira?
At most, I would think there's
two of them.
So it's two out of seven...
If we're prepared to let them know
that the investigation is
catching up to them,
then let's risk it on those odds.
I'm going to borrow
the name "L", Ryuzaki.
From the sound of the conversation...
the one who seems the least
likely to be Kira
and who carries some
weight on the board is...
- Ooi!
- Namikawa.
If you're going to make a call,
use this phone.
It can't be traced or tapped.
I really think it would
be faster if...
we killed the executives of
our rival companies one by one.
That would be going a bit far.
Let's kill them and
split their stocks.
You're Reiji Namikawa,
the V.P. of Yotsuba Group's
Sales Department One, aren't you?
Yes. So what about it?
Listen and respond as you see fit.
I am L.
I have cameras and wiretaps
planted in that meeting room...
and I'm recording footage
of your entire meeting.
The opening topic was Hatori's death.
Now you're debating who to kill.
Isn't that right?
He's been watching everything.
If you aren't Kira...
or if you aren't someone who
can directly contact Kira...
then let's make a deal.
A deal?!
Delay the death of E.L.F.'s president
and Mr. Zenzai one month.
This shouldn't be difficult for you.
- Yes, I see...
- If we want to randomize the deaths...
- Yes... Go on...
- we should just throw darts at a calendar.
If you do this,
and cooperate with us from now on,
your crime...no...
everyone other than
Kira will not be charged...
under the belief that they were
threatened by Kira
into participating in the meetings.
Ah... I see...
My only option is join L.
No, I'll be killed if Kira finds out
that I've sided with L.
What should I do?
If you reveal this conversation,
it'll cause a panic.
There would be no advantage for you.
Everyone will be caught.
But my goal is to go
one on one against Kira.
Listen... If L wins against Kira,
you'll be acquitted.
If Kira wins against me,
you'll carry on with your luxurious life.
Or you can remain a spectator and
go along with either side.
Whoever wins, L or Kira,
it's no loss to you.
However, it would be a loss
to you if you were caught right now.
He's already knows the answer
I would have given.
That's all...
Okay. On Monday...
What's wrong, Namikawa?
Who was it from?
Nothing, a subordinate of mine
messed up
and I'll have to fix it on Monday.
Sorry for interrupting.
Let's get back on topic.
Regarding when we should kill
those E.L.F. guys and Zenzai.
How about this?
How about we give Coil one month
to discover L's identity.
If he doesn't, we'll be forced to
kill them at various dates.
Next, we'll give him another month
and repeat the process.
Once we've dealt with L,
we'll go back to two to
three people a week.
In other words, we should make
dealing with L our first priority.
I see...
Indeed. If we kill L,
we won't have anything in our way.
Until then, we should be careful...
Yeah... It sounds good to me.
Well, we've got to be
extremely careful.
Then we'll give Coil one month.
No objections.
L...you're probably satisfied with this.
But we'll still hold these meetings
every week.
That's all for now.
It went well...
Yeah...
You really are amazing.
Not only did you delay the killing,
we may be able to get
information from Namikawa.
Furthermore, it looked like
something I would do...
You thought of it faster than I did.
At this rate...
if I die, it's quite possible you would be
capable of succeeding the title of L.
Why are you talking about
such morbid things?
We have a month to figure out
Kira's identity
and gather evidence against him.
The challenge is just beginning.
Yes...
But you're the one who
first noticed Yotsuba.
You may be more capable than I am.
You might be able to do it.
If I die...
would you take over for me as L?
If I die, would you take over for me?
As L.
If this is all an act and he is Kira,
he's sure to say yes...
What are you talking about, Ryuzaki?
As long as we have this,
won't we die together?
I see...
Ryuzaki...
Sorry, but I'm going to tell everyone
what you were thinking.
Ryuzaki thinks that if I'm Kira,
either I'm just pretending I'm not him
and putting on an act...
or Kira's power has passed
to someone else...
and I have no memory
that I was Kira.
Those two possibilities.
If it's the first...
If I'm putting on an act,
these handcuffs will never come off.
No, even if it was
the other possibility,
he probably wouldn't take them off.
Ryuzaki thinks that I'm Kira.
Even if that power has been
passed to someone else...
he assumes that I would have
planned things
to have it return to me again.
In other words, he doesn't think
I was being controlled.
I passed the power on
and planned for it to come back
to me once I've been cleared.
Amazing...You figured out exactly
what I was thinking.
Ryuzaki's line of reasoning is,
"Light will become Kira
once he steals L's position."
Correct.
To acquire the position of L...
and be able to freely control
the police,
while being Kira in secret...
would be the ultimate.
I could do that...no, I would do it.
That's what you meant, didn't you?
Yes.
But what about now?
You should know by now that
I'm probably not acting.
If you were acting and
trying to steal my position...
there's no way that you'd reveal
your plan in front of everyone.
Is that what you mean?
Ryuzaki...
Even after I catch the current Kira...
do you really think...
that I'd become Kira, a murderer?
Do I look like that kind of person?
I think so. You look it.
Again...?
Okay! Once is enough!
Let's just leave it as a draw!
I guess so.
At any rate, we have
to catch the Kira before us.
As long as I have the handcuffs,
you shouldn't have any complaints.
I suppose so.
We only have a month.
Ryuzaki...
Yes?
If we can use that meeting
as evidence against those seven,
won't the murders of criminals stop?
Again...
Unfortunately, no.
No?
We're not sure if Kira
is among those seven.
If they just have a connection to him,
Kira will simply kill them.
We have to be absolutely sure
that Kira is among them,
or there's no point in
catching them now.
Even if he is...
it's difficult to determine
who's Kira right now.
I think it's still too early.
But, if you can't say that
he's definitely among the seven...
there's still a chance that the killings
will stop if we arrest them.
It's like my dad says.
There is a chance.
Um, on second thought...
I think I'll go after Kira by myself.
You can use these headquarters,
as will l.
You can do things your way
and arrest them if you wish.
I shall investigate as
I wish in my own way.
We'll only get into arguments
if we don't.
Let's split and act separately.
In other words, you just want to
figure out who Kira is, huh?
Yes. This case will never be
solved if we don't capture him.
I won't say that stopping
the deaths
of people before us is pointless.
But if we don't find the truth,
Kira will appear again and
the victims will increase in the end.
That's why... I think it's more important
to figure out who Kira is.
I'm opposed to arresting those seven,
if you want to do that,
then you take responsibility for it.
I will pursue Kira by myself.
We only have one month.
I wonder who will be faster?
Ryuzaki...
Where are you going?
Amane's room.
Sorry Light, I know you're
on your father's side, but...
I can't remove these handcuffs,
so you're going to have to come with me.
Light! Was today a day
we could go on a date?
Along with Mr. Ryuzaki...
Misa...
Do you love Light?
Huh?
Yes...very much...
But you also worship Kira.
Yes...
So...
Who would you pick, Light or Kira?
Huh?
Light, of course.
I'm grateful to Kira and
wanted to meet him,
but that's not love. Definitely Light.
Light wants to catch Kira.
Isn't that right, Light?
Yeah. Of course.
He wants to catch him.
Now what'll you do?
If Light wants to catch him,
then I want Light to catch him.
So would you want to help
Light by working with him...
on the investigation?
Ryuzaki.
Yeah! I'll do anything for Light!
Wait a second.
What are you thinking of doing?
Aiber will pose as Eraldo Coil
and tell those seven that...
he learned that Misa Amane might
be able to identify L.
And that L brought her in
for questioning
because he suspected that
she was the Second Kira.
Well, that is true.
If they know that Misa Amane
might know L...
they'll have her appear in
their commercials
and try to ask her about
various things.
Since Mr. Matsuda's screw up...
there were talks about using her
in their commercials.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's no good.
Why?
Because it would subject
you to danger.
Huh?! You're worried about me?
All right!
But this is nothing if it's for you.
Listen Misa, if they know that
you might know who L is...
we don't know what means they'll use
to get that information out of you.
It's all right. I won't say anything
under any kind of torture.
Yes. That's true...
Besides, Kira can control
his victims' actions before death.
There is a good chance that
he might try to get her
to talk and kill her.
No, if he kills L, then he won't have
any use for her and
Kira would kill Misa to keep her silent.
I wouldn't like that...
Light.
If we win, Misa won't die.
Besides...
as long as we're handcuffed,
we'll share the same fate.
If I die, you'll die too.
In that case, Misa is the one
who would grieve the most.
It's either we both die,
or we catch Kira.
Now which will it be?
Catch Kira!
I can't live in a world without Light.
Yes, that's correct.
Hey, Ryuzaki, that's messed up.
We have no time.
I'm desperate.
Besides, Misa Amane's...
bravery and love for you...
have no equal.
Ryuzaki...
I think I've misunderstood
you all this time.
I called you a pervert and stuff.
You really do understand me!
Yes. Misa is the perfect,
most worthy woman for Light.
Yay!
Thank you, Ryuzaki.
I could fall in love with you,
you know.
Uh... That's a little...
How about being friends, Ryuzaki?
Yes.
I've made another friend.
Yeah. All of Light's friends are my friends.
Let's all be friends!
Yay!
And I won't ever betray
any of my friends.
With our powers combined,
let's arrest Kira!
No, but...
Yagami is taking a different investigative
approach from us
and working with
his father and the others.
You and I will be together, Misa.
Huh? What's with that?
That's dirty, Ryuzaki.
Now my only choice is to
join your investigation...
No, that's quite all right.
What are you talking about?
Light will be joining us!
No, it's not like that...
I'm opposed to this investigation.
It's too dangerous for you.
Light...
Thank you for thinking about me.
But let me do this.
I want to be of use to you.
I want to be of use to you and
I want you to love me even more.
Besides that, l...
would gladly die for you.
Arresting seven people in
this situation is difficult.
Mogi, Matsuda,
do you have any good ideas?
This single page Forever depressing
A fleeting tactic in the eyes
Without petition evil against the law
chain it in prison
Poison the notebook fear the lust
Delusion of being deceived
perpetually drooling
Judgement is "crime control" they driveled
Who has the Rx for that?
A decriminalized world
A sanctioned word
Taking in heat
Just like "Pirates of Death"
Atone with the game of laws
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
Billy in despair
Now, it's time for ethics
Now, the unstoppable Eraser Rain
The unstoppable Eraser Rain
Well, I am an actress.
Director Nishinaka, Light, the others...
And now even the Shinigami's
asking me to act!
This is a lot of work.
It looks like I might be in a big commercial.
I am so popular!